Careful now!
Don't feed her too much!
Don't do it!
I'm sorry, I can't remove the bean sound.
Unless you guys write, Liz.
This is on you, guys.
You kept feeding her, stop!
Oh, that's funny.
Can you guys hear me fine?
Hello, hello, hello?
Check, check, check.
Beem.
Okay, okay, good.
Alright, guys.
It's time that we continue.
Hold on, let me change the music a little bit.
It's getting a little ridiculous.
Beem.
I can't stop the sound of that, I'm sorry.
Don't give her too much!
Yeah, stop!
She's had enough!
He's not a hamster, you know.
So how you guys doing?
You guys doing alright?
Poor Yuri, Oliver, stop!
I'm not doing anything!
You guys!
This is on you!
I have done nothing.
I've just laid down the chessboard.
You guys are playing the game.
Beem.
Oh, that's hilarious.
Alright, guys.
It's time...
It's time for some, uh...
Doki Doki Literature Club.
I think I remember some of the voices I did, but we're gonna have to see how it goes.
I...
Yeah, I do remember some of the names.
Yuri, uh...
Say...
Sayori?
I think?
And then we have...
Megan?
Wait, I forgot that one's name.
It was not Megan, it was something with Emma.
Beem.
And then we had, uh...
Let me think.
I forgot the last one.
Wasn't it Megan?
What was the name?
Who the hell is Megan?
Beem.
I know it's not Megan, but it's something with M.
Monica!
That's right.
Monica.
That was close.
Come on.
It's just so absurd.
Everything about this is so stupid.
Someone on Discord was like...
You still remember the plot?
And I legitimately was like...
I don't...
What plot are you speaking of?
There was no plot.
Beem.
Not that I remember.
But I mean, I do remember some things.
I became part of the literature club and everyone wants to have sex with me, apparently.
These four girls.
And they're also all super depressed on top of it all.
So it's a nice little weird cocktail of, you know...
Emotions.
It's a ballet of emotions.
For sure.
Oh...
Oh man.
Hold on, I'm gonna...
I'm gonna increase the decay rate on this.
You guys are way too aggressive with the feeding.
I told you, you couldn't do it.
But you just kept going and going and going.
There we go.
What do you think?
Alright guys, you ready for Minecraft?
I'm just kidding.
I saw someone write that.
But I'm not gonna play Minecraft.
We're playing...
Doki Doki.
Don't worry.
But that was a good idea for a troll though.
Man, I should have done that.
I didn't even think about it.
That's genius.
Wow.
She looks ridiculous, I know.
It's so dumb.
Holy shit.
Oh my god.
Okay, I'm trying to remember what happened.
So I was at Yuri's house.
And...
She apparently also has a thing with scissors.
Like, I have a suspicion that she may be using them to do things to herself.
Which is not great.
So everyone's just depressed.
Pretty much.
It's kinda messed up.
And...
I also rejected...
What's her name?
The other one.
The childhood friend.
And that's pretty much what I remember.
Oh yeah, and they have fucked up poems.
Oh, and by the way, I launched the game and...
Something weird happened.
Hold on.
Let me switch over.
I didn't want to click on anything.
Bean.
Also, god, I hope that bean sound is not happening while I'm in a different scene.
I didn't even test that.
Let's see.
There's no sound?
Or what?
It says log in.
Oops.
What the hell is this?
Whoops.
Huh?
I swear to god, this wasn't there last time.
I don't know.
Well, there we go.
What the hell was that just now?
It's like a pre-menu to the menu.
Uh, where was I?
Must be this one.
541.
Wait, that's not right, is it?
No, wait, hold on.
646.
730.
No, it's this one.
Wait, hold on.
730.
Autosave.
Hmm.
I think I'll just take this one.
You can use the skip button to fast-forward through text you've already read.
Okay.
Oh, it's the day of the- That's right!
I stopped right before the festival!
That's true.
One sec.
Okay, sorry.
I just had to sneeze.
Or whatever.
Let's see here.
Of all days, I expected this to be the one where I'd be walking to school with Sayori.
Man, I forgot the other girl's name.
Sayori.
Yuri.
Monica, and the last one I totally forgot.
But Sayori isn't answering her phone.
I considered going to her house to wake her up, but decided that's a little too much.
Meanwhile, the preparations for the event should be nearly complete.
Right, we made banners and stuff, with colors and all that.
The banner Yuri and I painted is dry, and I gently rolled it up to take it with me.
She sent me a pleasant text, reminding me not to forget anything, and I reassured her.
Hold on.
I need to clean my glasses.
When there's a static screen on your monitor, that's when you really notice how dirty your glasses are.
I can't see shit.
There we go.
Funnily enough, I probably feel the same way as Natsuki about the event, that's right.
I always thought that funnily enough was like wrong English.
I kept saying it myself, you know, like funnily enough.
It just sounds wrong.
This sounds wrong.
But whatever.
I'm more excited for it to be over so I can spend time with Sayori and Yuri at the festival.
Am I?
But knowing Monica, I'm sure the event will be great too.
That's right, we had like different roles or whatever.
Wait, there's no sound!
Is this Bakht or what?
This feels weird.
OLIVER!
Oh wait, it's Monica.
Oh god, what voice did I give her?
Uh...
Probably like...
I don't remember.
You're the first one here!
That's the voice she's gonna get now.
Thanks for being early!
That's funny.
I thought at least Yuri would be here by now.
Monica is placing little booklets on each of the desks in the classroom.
They must be the ones she prepared that have all the poems we're performing.
Oh right, we're doing that!
Oh no.
Did I even figure out what my poem was?
People didn't like it, it seemed.
In the end, I found a random poem online that I thought Monica would like and submitted it.
Really?
So that's the one I'll be performing.
Wow, what a slacker.
I'm surprised you didn't bring Sayori with you!
Yeah, she overslept again, if you know what I mean.
That dummy.
You'd think that on days this important, she'd try a little harder.
I say that, but I suddenly remember what Sayori told me yesterday.
I don't remember.
And I suddenly feel awful, knowing it's not nearly that simple for her.
Oh yeah, right, I rejected her.
I only said it because it's the way I'm used to thinking.
Yeah, and we don't want to lie to her, right?
But...
Maybe I should have gone to wake her up after all.
What?
Why?
Ahaha!
You should take a little responsibility for her, Oliver!
I mean, especially after your exchange with her yesterday.
How do you know about that?
Excuse me?
I had a talk with Yuri...
And Sayori.
You weren't there.
You kinda left her hanging this morning, you know?
Exchange?
Monica...
You know about that?
Of course I do.
I'm the club president after all.
But...
I stammer, embarrassed.
Did Sayori really tell her about it that quickly?
I guess that's how girls operate, right?
They share everything.
About how I basically turned down her confession.
That makes me really seem like the bad guy here.
No, it doesn't.
But I'm the one who knows what's best for her, right?
What?!
No, I'm not!
What the hell kind of mindset is that?!
Jeez!
You don't know the full story at all, so...
Don't worry.
I probably know a lot more than you think.
Eh?
Monica is being as friendly as usual.
But for some reason I've felt a chill down my spine after hearing that.
Dude, I don't... I don't understand...
Like, there is sound, right?
There is sound, right?
There is sound.
That's so weird, there's no music.
Hey, do you wanna check out the pamphlets?
I hate this pose.
They came out really nice.
Oh yeah?
Prove it.
I grab one of the pamphlets laid out on the desks.
Oh yeah!
They really did, I say...
Sarcastically.
Something like this will definitely help people take the club more seriously.
Yeah, I thought so too.
I flipped through the pages.
Each member's poem is neatly printed on its own page.
Giving it an almost professional feel.
By the way!
I was conflicted, actually, after last time, whether or not I even wanted to continue this game.
But at this point, it's more...
Like, I am not, like, completely in love with this at all.
You know?
Like, I feel like everything up to this point has been kinda...
Like, not good.
You know what I mean?
Like, I don't wanna shit too much on it, but it's kinda not that great.
And, at this point, I'm more like...
It's a short game, right?
I just kinda wanna see it to the end.
Also because people love it so much, so I'm kinda curious, you know?
Like, maybe it'll win me over later, I don't know, I doubt it, but we'll see.
Just wanted to put that up.
I recognize Natsuki's and Yuri's poems from the ones they performed during our practice.
What's this?
I flipped to Sayori's poem.
It's different from the one she practiced.
Oh yeah?
It's one that I haven't read before.
Oh god, it's probably about me.
Get out of my head.
Okay, so Sayori is...
Not doing too great.
Get out of my head before I do what I know is best for you.
Get out of my head before I listen to everything she said to me.
Get out of my head before I show you how much I love you.
Get out of my head before I finish writing this poem.
But a poem is never actually finished.
It just stops moving.
Huh?
I mean, she's talking to me.
I don't know what the percentage sign is here, but...
It's like, I want you out of my head.
What's that song?
Out of my head, my head, my head, my head.
Something about like, you know.
There's a song like that.
Ah!
What's this?
Reading the poem, I get a pit in my stomach.
Oliver?
What's wrong?
Ah, nothing.
This poem feels completely different from everything else Sayori's written.
I can't wait to see her perform it.
I hope she's going to be verbatim saying everything.
But more than that...
I...
I changed my mind.
I'm gonna go get Sayori, so...
Ah!
Well, alright.
Try not to take too long, okay?
Ah, sure.
I quickly leave the classroom.
Don't strain yourself!
I hear in the distance.
Monica calls out that after me.
I really butchered that one, didn't I?
I quicken my pace.
I like that sentence.
What was I thinking?
I should have tried a little bit harder for Sayori.
No, I shouldn't.
I...
It's not the girl I want.
I want Yuri.
It's not a big deal to at least wait for her, or...
help her wake up.
What...
Why?
Even the simple gesture of walking her to school makes her really happy.
Besides, I told her yesterday that things will be the same as they always have been.
That's all she needs, and what I want to give her.
I reach Sayori's house and knock on the door.
I don't expect an answer, since she's not picking up her phone either.
I'm getting a really bad feeling about this.
Like yesterday, I opened the door and let myself in.
Sayori?
She really is a heavy sleeper.
Yeah, keep telling yourself that.
I swallow.
I can't believe I ended up doing this after all.
Waking her up in her own house?
Isn't that more like something a boyfriend would do?
Also, just walking into her house?
It's kinda fucked up, isn't it?
In any case...
It just feels right.
Does it?
Outside Sayori's room, I knock on her door.
Sayori?
Wake up, dummy!
There's no response.
I really didn't want to have to enter her room like this.
You can't just enter someone's room like this, let alone house!
Isn't it kind of a breach of privacy?
Yes!
It is!
But she really leaves me no choice.
I gently open the door.
Oh!
Jesus fucking Christ, that scared me!
I fucking figured something like this would happen.
Wow, they're actually showing that.
What the hell?
An exception has occurred.
Wait, what?
Are we inside a simulation?
Nothing's real.
See traceback for details?
How do I open the traceback?
What the hell?
Okay, at least we confirmed the music is working.
What the hell?!
Is this a nightmare?
Oh, is it a dream?
It has to be.
This isn't real.
Yeah, that's what I said.
It's fake.
There's no way this can be real.
Sayori wouldn't do this.
I don't know about that.
But the fact that they're showing all this...
Everything was normal up until a few days ago.
That's why I can't believe what my eyes are showing me.
I suppressed the urge to vomit.
Just yesterday.
I told Sayori I would be there for her.
I told her I know what's best, and that everything will be okay.
Then why?
Why would she do this?
How could I be so helpless?
What did I do wrong?
Nothing.
Turning down her confession?
That has to have been what pushed her over the edge.
Her agonized scream still echoes in my ears.
Why did I do that to her when she needed me the most?
Well, what should I have done?
Giving her false hope is the worst thing I could have done.
Why was I so selfish?
You were not.
It's not your fault.
My swarming thoughts keep telling me everything I could have done to prevent this.
If I just spent more time with her.
Walked her to school.
And gave her what I know she wanted out of our relationship.
So you wanted to give her fake love?
To make her not kill herself?
That sounds like a bad idea, dude.
Then I could have prevented this.
No.
I know I could have prevented this.
Screw the literature club.
Fuck yeah.
Screw the festival.
I just lost my best friend.
Someone I grew up with.
She's gone forever now.
What is this creepy ass music?
Nothing I do can bring her back.
This isn't some game where I can reset and try something different.
Is it not?
I had only one chance.
And I wasn't careful enough.
And now I'll carry this guilt with me until I die.
Nothing in my life is worth more than hers.
But I still couldn't do what she needed from me.
God, are you just gonna keep repeating this?
And now...
I can never take it back.
Never.
And?
What?
What the fuck?
What's... uh...
Wait a minute, is that...
Is this...
Sayori?
Wait, hold on.
So, this is Yuri.
Wait, who's who?
This is not Suki.
This has to be...
Wait a minute, why do they look exactly the same?
They have the same pen.
Wait, what the fuck is this?
I see an annoying girl running toward me from the distance, waving her arms in the air like she's totally oblivious to any attention she might draw to herself.
That girl is...
My neighbor and good friend since we were children.
You know, the kind of friend you'd never see yourself making today, but kinda just it of works out because you've known each other so long for.
We used to walk to school together on days like this, but starting around high school she would weekend more and more frequently and I would get tired of waiting up.
But if she's gonna chase after me like this, I nearly feel better off running away.
However, I just sigh an idol in front of the crosswalk and it's up to me.
Yeah, okay.
It's an ordinary school day, like any other.
Mornings are usually the worst, being surrounded by friends and couples, groups walking to school together.
Meanwhile, I've always walked to school alone.
I always tell myself it's about time I meet some girls or something like that.
But I have no motivation to join any clubs.
I'm perfectly content just getting by on the average, while spending my free time anime on games.
There's always the anime club, but it's not like there would be any girls in it anyway.
The school day is as ordinary as ever, and it's over before I know it.
After I pack up my things, I stare blankly at the wall, looking for an ounce of motivation.
Clubs!
There really aren't any that interest me.
Besides, most of them would probably be way too demanding for me to want to deal with.
I guess I have no choice but to start with the anime club.
Oliver?
Monica?
Oh my goodness, I totally didn't expect to see you here!
It's been a while, right?
Uh, yeah!
It has!
Monica smiles sweetly.
We do know each other well.
We rarely talk, but we were in the same class last year.
Monica was probably the most popular girl in class.
Smart, beautiful, athletic.
Basically completely out of my league.
Wait a minute, have I read this before?
So having her smile on me so genuinely feels a little...
What did you come in here for anyway?
Oh, I've just been looking for some supplies to use for my club!
Do you know if there's any construction paper in here?
Or... markers?
I guess you can check the closet.
You're the debate club, right?
Haha, about that.
I actually quit it.
Really, you quit?
Yeah.
To be honest, I can't stand all the politics around the major clubs.
It feels like nothing but arguing about the budget and publicity and how to prepare for the events.
I'd much rather take something I personally enjoy and make something special out of it.
In that case, what club did you decide to join?
Actually, I'm starting a new one.
A literature club!
Fucking hell, that scared me.
Literature!
That sounds kinda dull!
How many members do you have so far?
Um...
It's kind of embarrassing, but...
There are only three of us so far?
It's really hard to find new...
Wait, three!
Alright!
It's really hard to find new members or something that sounds so boring!
Well, I can see that!
But it's really not boring at all, you know?
Literature can be anything!
Reading, writing, poetry...
I mean, one of my members even keeps her manga collection in the club room!
Wait, really?!
Yeah, it's funny, right?
She always insists that manga is literature too!
I mean, she's not wrong, I guess.
And besides, a member's a member, right?
Did Monica say she?
Hey, Oliver!
By any chance, are you still looking for a club to join?
Ah!
I mean, I guess so, but...
In that case...
Is there any chance you would do me a big favor?
I won't ask you to join, but...
If you could get, at the very least, or visit my club, it would make me really happy!
Please?
Um...
Well, I guess I have no reason to refuse!
Besides, how could I ever refuse someone like Monica?
Sure, I guess I could check it out!
Ah!
Awesome!
You're really sweet, Oliver, you know that?
It's nothing!
Really?
Shall we go then?
I'll look for the materials another time!
You're more important!
Oh, thank you!
And thus, today marks the day I sold my soul to Monica, and her irresistible smile.
Wait, was it Monica last time too?
I dejectedly follow Monica across the school and upstairs.
A section of the school I rarely visit.
Monica, full of energy, swings open the classroom door.
And I brought a guest with me!
Oh!
A... guest?
Seriously?
You brought a boy?!
Way to kill the atmosphere!
Don't be mean, Natsuki!
But anyway, welcome to the club, Oliver!
Ah...
All words escape me in this situation.
This club...
is full of incredibly cute girls!
So let me guess...
You're Monica's boyfriend, right?
What?!
No!
I'm not!
Natsuki...
The girl with the sour attitude, whose name is apparently Natsuki, is one I don't recognize.
Her small figure makes her look like a first year student.
Anyway, this is Natsuki, energetic as usual.
And this is Yuri, the Vice President.
I... it's nice to meet you.
Yuri, who appears comparably more mature and timid, seems to have a hard time keeping up with someone like Natsuki.
Yeah...
It's nice to meet both of you.
So I ran into Oliver in a classroom, and he decided to come check out the club!
Isn't that great?
Wait!
Monica!
Didn't I tell you to let me know in advance before you brought anyone new?
I was gonna... well...
You know...
Sorry, sorry.
I didn't forget that, but I just happened to run into him.
In that case, I should at least make some tea, right?
Yeah, that would be great!
Why don't you come sit down, Oliver?
The girls have a few desks arranged to form a table.
Bro, what is happening in this game right now?
Yuri walks to the corner of the room and opens the closet.
Meanwhile, Monica and Natsuki sit across from each other.
Still feeling awkward, I take a seat next to Monica.
So, I know you didn't really plan on coming here.
But we'll make sure you feel right at home, okay?
As president of the Literature Club, it is my duty to make the club fun and exciting for everyone.
I'm surprised there aren't more people in the club yet!
It must be hard to start a new club!
You could put it that way.
Not many people are very interested in putting out all the effort to start something brand new.
Especially when it's something that doesn't grab your attention, like literature.
You have to work hard to convince people that you're both fun and worthwhile.
But you make school events like the festival that much more important.
I'm confident that we can all really grow this club together before we graduate.
Right, Natsuki?
Well...
I guess.
Natsuki reluctantly agrees.
Such different girls, all interested in the same goal.
Monica must have worked really hard just to find these two.
Dude, I still can't get over the fact that they showed that girl hanged from the ceiling.
Like, what the fuck?
That's messed up, bro.
Yuri returns to the table, carrying a tea set.
She carefully places a tea cup in front of each of us before setting down the teapot in the middle.
You keep a whole te- YOU KEEP A WHOLE TEA SET IN THIS CLASSROOM!
Don't worry.
The teachers gave us permission.
After all, doesn't a hot cup of tea help you enjoy a good book?
Uh, I guess?
Haha, don't let yourself get intimidated.
Yuri's just trying to impress you.
Huh, that's not...
Insulted, Yuri looks away.
I meant that, you know.
I believe you.
Well, tea and reading might not be a pastime for me, but I at least enjoy tea.
I'm glad.
Yuri faintly smiles to herself in relief.
So, Oliver, what kinds of things do you like to read?
Well, uh...
Considering how little I've read these past few years, I don't really have a good way of answering that.
MANGA!
I mutter quietly to myself, half-joking.
Natsuki's head suddenly perks up.
It looks like she wants to say something, but she keeps quiet.
N-not much of a reader, I guess.
Well, that can change.
What am I saying?
I spoke without thinking after seeing Yuri's sad smile.
Also...
Sayori isn't here.
Anyway, what about you, Yuri?
Well, let's see.
Yuri traces the rim of her teacup with her finger.
My favorites are usually novels that build deep and complex fantasy worlds.
The level of creativity and craftsmanship behind them is amazing to me.
And telling a good story in such a foreign world is equally impressive.
Yuri goes on, clearly passionate about her reading.
She seemed so reserved and timid since the moment I walked in.
But it's obvious by the way her eyes light up that she finds her comfort in the world of books, not people.
But you know, I like a lot of things.
Stories with deep psychological elements usually immerse me as well.
Isn't it amazing how a writer can so deliberately take advantage of your own lack of imagination to completely throw you for a loop?
Anyway, I've been reading a lot of horror lately.
Ah!
I read a horror book once!
I desperately grasp something I can relate to at the minimal level.
At this rate, Yuri might as well be having a conversation with a rock.
Ahaha!
I'd expect that from you, Yuri.
It suits your personality.
Oh, is that so?
Really, if a story makes me think, or takes me to another world, then I really can't put it down.
Surreal horror is often very successful at changing the way you look at the world.
If only for a brief moment.
Ugh!
I hate horror!
Oh, why's that...
Well, I just...
Natsuki's eyes dart over to me for a split second.
Never mind.
That's right, you usually like to write about cute things, don't you, Natsuki?
B-what?
Who gives you that idea?
You left a piece of scrap paper behind last club meeting.
It looked like you were working on a poem called...
Don't say it out loud!
And give that back!
Fine, fine.
Natsuki!
You write your own poems?!
Uh, well, I guess sometimes?
Why do you care?
I think that's impressive!
Why don't you share them sometime?
N-no!
Natsuki averts her eyes.
You wouldn't...
Like them!
Ah!
Not a very confident writer yet?!
I understand how Natsuki feels.
Sharing that level of writing takes more than just confidence.
The truest form of writing is writing to oneself.
You must be willing to open up to your readers, exposing your vulnerabilities, and showing even the deepest reaches of your heart.
Do you have writing experience too, Yuri?
Maybe if you share some of your work, you can set an example, and help Natsuki feel comfortable enough to share hers!
I guess it's the same for Yuri!
We all sit in silence for a moment.
No, we're standing.
Hey, I just got an idea!
How about this?
Natsuki and Yuri look quizzically at Monika.
Let's all go home and write a poem of our own!
Oh god, please don't make me go through all that again.
I swear to god.
Then next time we meet, we'll all share them with each other!
That way everyone is even.
Um...
Ah!
I mean, I thought it was a good idea.
Well...
I think you're right, Monika.
We should probably start finding activities for all of us to participate in together.
I did decide to take on the responsibility of Vice President after all.
I need to do my best to nurture the club as well as its members.
Besides, now that we have a new member, it seems like a good step for us to take.
Do you agree as well, Oliver?
Hold on!
There's still one problem!
Eh?
What's that?
Now that we've reached the most important topic, I bluntly come forth with what's been on my mind the entire time.
I never said I would join this club!
Monika may have convinced me to stop by, but I never made any decision!
I still have other clubs to look at and, um...
I lose my train of thought.
All three girls stare back at me with dejected eyes.
But, but...
I'm sorry.
I thought...
Huh!
The girls exchange glances before Monika turns back to me.
I... I guess I need to tell you the truth, Oliver.
The thing is...
We don't have enough members yet to form an official club.
We need four.
And I've been trying really, really, really hard to find new members.
And if we don't find one more before the festival...
I...
I'm defenseless against these girls!
How am I supposed to make a clear-headed decision when it's like this?
I would feel terrible for letting everyone down in this situation.
And besides, the club itself seems pretty relaxed.
So if writing poems is the price I need to pay in order to spend every day with these beautiful girls...
Right!
Okay, I've decided then!
I'll join the Literature Club!
One by one, the girls' eyes light up.
Oh my goodness, really?
Do you really mean that, Oliver?
Yeah!
It could be fun, right?
You really did scare me for a moment.
I mean, if you really just left after all this, I would be super pissed.
Oliver, I'm so happy!
We can become an official club now!
Thank you so much for this!
You're really amazing!
The best person on earth!
Wow, can we thank you enough?!
I'll do everything I can to give you a great time, okay?
Ah-ha-ha!
Thanks!
I guess?
Okay, everyone!
I think with that, we can officially end today's meeting on a good note!
Everyone remember tonight's assignment!
Write a poem to bring to the next meeting so we can all share!
Monica looks over to me once more.
Oliver, I look forward to seeing how you express yourself!
He-he-he!
Can I really impress the class star Monica with my mediocre writing skills?
I already feel the anxiety welling up inside me.
Meanwhile, the girls continue to chit-chat as Yuri cleans up the tea set.
I guess I'll be on my way then!
Okay!
I'll see you tomorrow then!
I can't wait!
Yeah, me neither.
Hold on, be right back.
Alright.
With that, I depart the club room and make my way home.
The hallway.
My mind wanders back and forth between the three girls.
Natsuki.
Yuri.
And of course, Monica.
There's no Sayori!
Will I really be happy spending every day after school in a literature club?
Wait, is my goal to kill all these girls?
We're gonna run out of girls!
Yo!
Is that it?
Is that the dark fucking shit that's going on here?
God, I hope not.
Perhaps I'll have the chance to grow closer to one of these girls.
The main character, me, in this game is actually a freaking psycho.
He is joining all these clubs around the country.
Making girls interested in him and then rejecting them.
I'll just need to make the most of my circumstances and I'm sure good fortune will find me.
And I guess that starts with writing a poem tonight.
Oh yeah, let's do that!
Let's...
Wait.
You've unlocked a special poem.
Would you like to read it?
Yes.
Can you hear me?
Was that the special poem?
Damn, son.
Hmm.
Wait, why are there only two girls?
I'm so confused right now.
I'm trying to understand what's happening here.
Also, I should probably save the game.
Wait a minute.
I don't think my saves are gone.
I think the game is fucking with me somehow.
But whatever.
Uh...
So we have, uh...
Yuri?
And we have...
Uh...
I think Natsuki?
But I'm gonna...
We're gonna try a 2020 Yuri here.
Here we go.
You ready?
Let's see if I remember this.
I would say, uh...
Probably...
Incongruent.
Yeah!
Starscape.
Uh...
Heaven Sent.
No, wait.
Uh...
Not that one.
Maybe, uh...
Uh...
Yeah!
Good!
What about...
Could be special?
Or...
Empty!
Yes!
Destiny!
And...
Oh god.
Analysis?
What else?
I don't know what Vivacious means.
Sugar Dream Lazy.
Uh...
Let's go with, uh...
Vivacious.
Nice!
Philosophy?
I'm so good at this.
Actually amazing.
After Image could be it.
She likes horror, right?
Fuck yeah!
Probably Massacre too?
Wait a minute.
Is she gonna end up murdering a whole class?
I hope not.
Intellectual maybe?
Unrequited?
Uh, probably this one.
Yes!
Existence.
So far I nailed them all.
Uh...
Oh god.
I don't know.
This one's tough.
The Spice, Prayer...
Fester, Cheeks, Crimson...
Ooh, this is a tough one!
Maybe Memories.
Fuck!
I messed it up!
Oh my god!
I wonder what happens when you get 20 out of 20!
Oh, well now it doesn't matter anymore.
Let me just do Unrestrained.
Variance.
Uh...
Let's see here...
Suicide is oddly fitting right now, but let's do...
What the hell is Kawaii?
Reminds me of Hawaii.
You know the island?
Whistle the...
Probably...
Hope?
Nice!
Okay.
Entropy?
Uncanny I would say?
Ambient?
Nice!
Uh, let's do...
Depression?
Oh my god, okay!
And the last one...
I would say Contamination.
Fuck yeah!
I got 19 out of 20!
I can't believe I messed one up.
Hi again, Oliver!
Glad to see you didn't run away on us!
Nah, don't worry!
This might be a little strange for me, but...
I at least keep my word.
Well, I'm back at the Literature Club.
I was the last to come in, so everyone else is already hanging out.
Thanks for keeping your promise, Oliver.
I hope this isn't too overwhelming of a commitment for you.
Making you dive headfirst into literature when you're not accustomed to it.
Uh...
Did she just come down with an umbrella?
Oh, come on!
Like he deserves any slack.
You already had to be dragged here by Monica.
I don't know if you plan to just come here and hang out or what.
But if you don't take it seriously, then you won't see the end of it!
Natsuki ablas- Wait, she's blocking the fucking text now!
Natsuki uncertainty have a big mouth!
For someone who keeps her manga collectibles in the classroom!
Natsuki finds herself stuck between saying Monica and Manga!
Monikanga!
Manga is literature!
Swiftly defeated, Natsuki plops back into her seat.
I'm sorry, Oliver.
We'll make sure to put your comfort first, okay?
Did she say that last time?
Wait, the music just made a weird turn.
Yuri shoots Natsuki with a disappointed glance.
Um, anyway...
Now that you're in the club and all...
Perhaps you might have interest in picking up a book to read?
Dude, I can't wait to feed her chocolate!
Well...
I can't really say no either way!
Like you said, I'm in this club now!
So it only feels right for me to do something like that, if you ask.
W-wait...
I didn't mean it like that.
Uh...
If you don't really want to, then forget I said anything, I guess.
Aha!
No, it's not that, Yuri!
I wanna try to be a part of this club!
So even if I don't read often, I'd be happy to pick up a book, even if you wanted me to!
Uh, are you sure?
I just... felt like...
Well, as...
VP and all...
That I should help you get started on something you might like?
Yuri reaches into her bag and pulls out a book.
I didn't want you to feel left out.
So I picked out a book that I thought you might enjoy.
It's a short read, so it should keep your attention, even if you don't usually read.
And we could...
You know...
Discuss it if you wanted.
Th-this is...
How is this girl accidentally being so cute?!
She even picked out a book she thinks I'll like, despite me not reading much.
Yuri, THANK YOU!
I'll definitely read this!
I enthusiastically take the book.
Phew.
Well, you can read it at your own pace.
I look forward to hearing what you think.
Now that everyone's settled in, I expected Monica to kick off some scheduled activities for the club.
But that doesn't seem to be the case!
Yuri's face is already buried in a book.
I can't help but notice her intense expression.
Like she was waiting for this chance.
Meanwhile, Natsuki is rummaging around in the closet.
I'm really curious to talk to Yuri a little bit more.
Hell yeah!
But at the same time, I would feel bad for distracting her from reading.
I catch a glimpse of the cover of her book.
It looks like the same book that she lent to me.
More than that, she seems to be on the first few pages!
Ah...
I think she noticed me looking at her!
She sneaks another glance at me, and her eyes meet for a split second.
But that only makes her hide her face deeper in her book.
Sorry!
I was just spacing out!
I muttered this, sensing I made her uncomfortable.
Oh...
It's fine.
If I was focused, then I probably wouldn't have noticed in the first place.
But I'm just rereading a bit of this, so...
That's the book that you gave me, right?!
What the fuck is going on with her face?!
I wanted to reread some of it.
Not for any particular reason.
Just curious!
How come you have two copies of the same book?!
Well...
When I stopped at the bookstore yesterday...
Ah...
That's not...
That's not what I meant.
I mean...
I...
Just happened...
To buy two of them?
Ah!
I see!
There's something fairly obvious here.
The jury isn't telling me!
But I decided to let it go!
The fact that a fucking eye was drifting off her face...
I'll definitely start reading it soon!
I'm glad to hear.
Once it starts to pick up...
You might have a hard time putting it down.
It's a very engaging and relatable story.
Is that so?!
What's the story about anyway?!
Well...
Look at the cover of the book!
The book is titled...
Portrait of Markov.
Holy shit!
She's into statistics!
And chains!
There's an ominous looking eye symbol on the front cover.
Basically, it's about this religious camp that was turned into a human experiment prison.
And the people trapped there have this trait that turns them into killing machines that lust for blood.
What?!
But the facility gets even worse!
And they start selectively breeding people by cutting off their limbs and affixing them to...
Oh, that might be a little bit of a spoiler.
But anyway, I'm really into it.
The book, I mean.
Not the thing about the limbs.
That's kind of...
That's kind of dark, isn't it?
Yuri made it sound like it was going to be a nice story.
So that dark turn came from nowhere.
Ah...
Are you not a fan of that sort of thing, Oliver?
No, it's not that!
I mean, I can definitely enjoy these kinds of stories!
So don't worry!
I hope so.
Yeah, I totally forgot that Yuri is into those things.
She's so shy and reclusive on the outside.
But her mind seems to be completely different.
It's just that this kind of story...
It's the kind that challenges you to look at life from a strange new perspective.
When horrible things happen not just because someone wants to be evil...
But because the world is full of horrible people and we're all worthless anyway...
Then suddenly...
I'm rambling, aren't I?
Not again.
I'm sorry.
Hey!
Don't apologize!
I haven't lost interest or anything!
Well...
I guess it's alright.
But I feel like I should let you know that I have this problem.
When I let things like books and writing fill my thoughts...
What?!
I kind of forget to pay attention to other people.
So I'm sorry if I end up saying something strange.
And please stop me if I'm...
Talking too much.
That's...
I really don't think you need to worry!
That just means you're a passionate...
Being!
The least I can do is listen!
It's a literature club after all!
Uh...
That's...
Well that's true.
In fact!
I might as well get started reading it, right?!
Yes!
I mean, you don't have to, but...
Haha!
What are you saying?!
Let me just get the book!
I quickly retrieve the book that I had put into my bag.
Alright!
It's fine if I sit here, right?!
I slip into the seat next to Yuri's.
Ah!
Yeah...
Are you sure?!
You seem a little apprehensive!
That's...
I'm sorry.
It's not that I don't want you to.
It's just something I'm not very used to.
That is...
Reading in company with someone who said this is so stupid.
I see!
Watch your dance!
Ah!
Ha ha ha ha ha!
Yes!
Well...
He he he he...
Okay...
Well...
I
can't do this stupid voice!
Ah, I need to calm down.
Okay, wait, wait.
Wait, hold on, give me a sec.
Okay, focus.
Focus, dammit.
Oh my god, I'm crying.
Wait, wait, what happened for this?
Uh... Which one is the latest?
I don't fucking understand.
Alright.
I can't fucking do it.
Oh my god.
Okay, focus.
Log in.
This is so stupid.
Well, just tell me if I've not distracted you or anything!
Alright.
I open the book and start the prologue.
I soon understand what Yuri means about reading and company.
It's as if I can feel a presence over my shoulder as I read.
It's not a particularly bad thing.
Maybe a little distracting, but the feeling is somewhat comforting.
Yuri is in the corner of my eye.
I realize that she's not actually looking at her own book.
I glance over.
It looks like she's reading from my book instead.
Sorry.
I was just bathing in the feeling.
Yuri, you really apologize a lot, don't you?
I... I do?
I don't really mean to.
Sorry.
I mean...
Here!
This should work, right?
I slide my desk until it's up against Yuri's.
And hold my book more between the two of them.
Ah...
I suppose so.
Yuri timidly closes her own copy.
Once we each lead in a little bit, our shoulders are almost touching.
It feels like my left arm is in the way, so instead I use my right hand to hold the book open.
Ah!
I guess that makes it kind of difficult to turn the page!
Here.
Oh, here we go.
Yuri takes her left arm and holds the left side of the book between her thumb and forefinger.
Ah!
I do the same with my right arm on the right side of the book.
That way I turn a page and Yuri slides it under her thumb after it flips to her side.
But in holding it like this, we're huddled even closer together than before.
It's actually kind of distracting me.
It's as if I can feel the warmth of Yuri's face, and she's in the corner of my vision.
Are you ready?
Huh?!
To turn the page...
Ha!
Sorry!
I think I got a bit distracted for a second!
I glance over at Yuri's face again, and our eyes meet.
I don't know how I'll be able to keep up with her.
Ah...
That's okay.
You're not as used to reading, right?
I don't mind being patient if it takes you a bit longer.
That's probably the least I can do.
Since you've been so patient with me.
Yeah!
Thanks!
We continue reading.
Yuri no longer asks me if I'm ready to turn the page.
Instead, I just assume that she finishes the page before me.
So I turn it by my own volition.
What if she never ends up finishing the page?!
Then I'm just being an asshole!
We continue the first chapter in silence.
Even so, turning each page almost feels like an intimate exchange.
Oh my god.
My thumb gently letting go of the page, letting it flutter over to her side as she catches it under her own thumb.
Hey Yuri!
This might be a silly thought, but...
The main character kind of reminds me of you a little bit!
Eh?
No, I don't relate to this character at all.
Definitely not.
Really?
I was just thinking the way she second guesses things she says and all that!
Ah.
That's what you were talking about.
Sorry.
I thought you meant... something else about her.
Something else?!
Never mind.
We didn't even get that far yet.
So I don't know why that came into my head.
Yuri!
Are you feeling alright?!
Huh?
Yuri's been a little fidgety ever since we started reading.
Oh my god.
Give me a moment.
Oh my god, this is horrible.
Come on, wake up man.
Fucking...
Pull yourself together.
Let's go.
Enter character.
You can rest if you're feeling sick or something!
Your breathing is a little...
My breathing?
Yuri puts her hand on her chest.
As if to feel her heartbeat.
I... I...
I didn't even notice.
Anyway, I'm... fine.
I just need some...
Water.
Alright!
Don't push yourself!
Yuri stands up and practically rushes out of the classroom.
What on earth was that about?
Oliver?
Did something happen just now?
Eh?
I've no idea.
Yuri was acting a little strange, I guess.
So you...
So you don't know anything?
Sorry, I can't say I do!
Are you worried about her?
No...
Not really.
I was just making sure that you didn't do anything to her.
No!
Nothing!
Don't worry, I believe you silly.
Yuri just does this sometimes, so it's nothing alarming.
Alright!
If you say so!
Anyway...
Why don't we start with sharing our poems with each other?
Eh?
Should we wait for Yuri?
Well, she might be a while.
So I just...
Get started without her.
Is that okay?
Yeah!
Oh my god!
I can't!
Dude, my cheeks are hurting.
Think of sad things.
Okay.
Yeah!
I was just asking!
I stand up.
I make a mental note of where I left off in the book.
Then slip it back into my bag.
Who should I show my poem to first?
Wait, uh, wait a minute.
What about Yuri?
Wait, where's...
She ran out to get water and now she's not here?
Or what?
Natsuki.
I told Natsuki I was interested in her poems yesterday.
Wait, what do you mean yesterday?
Was there a yesterday?
It's probably only fair if I shared mine with her first.
Oh yeah, right, we wrote a poem.
True.
What the fuck?!
Oliver, if you're not gonna take this club seriously, then go home!
Th- w-what?!
Harsh?!
What, you expect me to believe that you actually put effort into this?
Do you think I'm stupid?
I'm not a writer!
Maybe it's not very good, but yeah, I did put in effort!
We all start somewhere, right?!
If you're still proud of the first poem you ever wrote, then I'd like to read it!
Painful to think about?!
Fine.
Well, sorry.
You'll get better anyway.
I'd tell you what to improve, but you're better off just trying again.
Fair enough!
Well, to each their own, I guess.
Anyway, I guess I gotta share mine now.
Knowing you, you'll probably think it's stupid.
Eagles can fly, monkeys can climb, crickets can leap, horses can race, owls can seek, cheetahs can run, eagles can fly- But that's about it.
Yeah.
I told you that you weren't gonna like it.
I LIKE IT!
What?
Just be honest!
I am!
Why are you so convinced that I wouldn't like it?!
Well...
Because...
Everyone in high school thinks that writing has to be all sophisticated and stuff.
So people don't even take my writing seriously!
But isn't the point of poems for people to express themselves?!
Your writing style wouldn't make your message any less valid!
Yes, exactly!
I like it when it's easy to read, but it hits you hard.
Like in this poem.
Seeing everyone around you do great things can be really disheartening.
So I decided to write about it.
Yeah, I understand!
But the other nice thing about simple writing is that it puts more weight on the wordplay.
Like I set up for a rhyme at the end, but then made it fall flat on purpose.
It helps bring out the feeling in the last line.
So you did!
I guess more went into it than I realized!
That's what it means to be a pro.
I'm glad you learned something.
Didn't expect that from the youngest one here, did you?
Yeah!
I guess not!
I decide to humor her with that last comment.
I don't really care how old everyone is.
But if Natsuki is feeling proud, then I won't take that away from her.
Oh, let me guess...
Who should I pick next?
Monica!
Hi Oliver!
Having a good time so far?
Yeah!
Good!
Glad to hear it.
By the way, since you're new on everything...
If you ever have any suggestions for the club, like new activities or things we can do better...
I'm always listening.
Don't be afraid to bring things up, okay?
Alright!
I'll keep that in mind!
Of course I'll be afraid to bring things up.
I'm much better off just going with the flow until I'm more settled in.
Anyway...
Want to share your poem with me?
It's kind of embarrassing, but...
I guess I have to!
Don't worry, Oliver.
We're all a little embarrassed today, you know.
But it's that sort of barrier that we'll all learn to get past soon.
Yeah!
That's true!
I hand Monica my poem.
Mmm!
Great job, Oliver!
I almost got an ooh in my head while reading it.
It's really metaphorical.
I'm not sure why, but I didn't expect you to go for something so deep.
I guess I underestimated you.
It's easiest for me to keep everyone's expectations low.
That way, it always counts when I put in some effort!
That's not very fair.
Well, I guess it worked anyway.
You know that Yuri likes this kind of writing, right?
Writing that's full of imagery and symbolism?
Sometimes I feel like Yuri's mind is just totally detached from reality!
I don't mean that, like it's a bad thing though.
But sometimes I get the impression that she's just totally given up on people.
She spends so much time in her own head, and it's probably a much more interesting place for her.
But that's why she gets so happy when you treat her with a lot of kindness.
I don't think she's used to being indulged like that.
She must be really starved for social interaction.
So don't blame her for coming on a little strongly.
Like earlier.
Wait, what?
What do you mean?
Does she know about our reading session?
What's happening here?
I think if she gets too stimulated, she ends up withdrawing and looking for alone time.
Oh, is that what happened?
Suddenly the door opens.
I'm back.
Did I miss anything?
Not really.
Well, we all started sharing our poems with each other.
Yeah?
Already?
I'm sorry for being late.
No need to apologize.
We still have plenty of time, so I'm more glad that you took all the time you needed.
Alright.
Thanks, Monica.
I suppose I should go get my poem now.
Anyway, you wanna read my poem now?
Don't worry, I'm not very good.
You sound pretty confident for someone who claims to be not very good.
Well, that's because I have to sound confident.
That doesn't mean I always feel that way, you know?
I see!
Well, let's read it then!
Hole in wall.
Wait.
Is this the, uh...
The follow-up to bean in mouth?
But he wasn't looking at me.
Confused, I frantically glance at my surroundings.
But my burned eyes can no longer see color.
Are there others in this room?
Are they talking?
Or are they simply poems?
On flat sheets of paper!
The sound of frantic scrawling playing tricks on my ears.
The room begins to crinkle.
Closing in on me.
The air I breathe dissipates before it reaches my lungs.
I panic.
There must be a way out.
It's right there.
He's right there.
Swallowing my fears.
I brandish my pen.
So, what do you think?
Uh...
It's very, uh...
Freeform.
If that's what you call it.
Sorry, I'm not really the right person to ask for feedback.
Haha, it's okay.
Yeah, that kind of style has gotten pretty popular nowadays.
That is, a lot of poems have been putting emphasis on the timing between words and lines.
When performed out loud, it can be really powerful.
Was that the inspiration behind this one?
Well, I'm not sure if I know how to put it.
I guess you could say that I had some kind of epiphany recently.
It's been influencing my poems a bit.
An epiphany?
Yeah, something like that.
I'm kind of nervous to talk about deep stuff like that because it's kind of coming on strongly.
Maybe after everyone is better friends with each other.
Anyway.
Here's Monica's writing tip of the day!
Sometimes, when you're writing a poem or a story, your brain gets too fixated on a specific point.
If you try so hard to make it perfect, then you'll never make any progress.
Just force yourself to get something down on the paper and tidy it up later.
Another way to think about it is this.
If you keep your pen in the same spot for too long, you just get a big dark puddle of ink.
So just move your hand and go with the flow.
That's my advice for today!
Thanks for listening!
Oh god.
Oh, Yuri is here now!
Right!
Let's show her our poem.
This is the person we wrote the poem for in the first place.
As Yuri reads the poem, I notice her eyes lighten.
Exceptional.
Huh?!
What was that?!
D-did I say that out loud?
Yuri first covers her mouth, but then ends up covering her whole face!
Ooh!
He's gonna ha- Um...
You really didn't do anything wrong, Yuri!
Huh?
That's...
I...
I guess you're right.
What am I getting so nervous for?
Yuri takes a breath.
So...
What kind of writing experience do you have?
Your use of imagery and metaphors indicate you've written a lot of poetry before.
Really?!
Wow!
That's a huge compliment coming from you?!
This is actually my first time!
Really?!
Huh?
Yuri stares at me blankly, then looks at my poem again.
Well, I know that!
I just meant, uh...
Um...
Yuri trails off, unable to find an excuse.
She traces her finger along the words in the poem, as if breaking it down more thoroughly.
Yeah...
Okay.
This is the reason I was able to tell.
It's just that there are specific writing habits that are usually typical of new writers.
And having been through that myself, I kind of learned to pick up on them.
I think the most noticeable thing I recognize in new writers is that they try to make their style very deliberate.
In other words, they tend to pick a writing style separate from the topic matter.
And they form-fit the two together.
The end result is that both the style and the expressiveness are weakened.
Once Yuri finds her train of thought, it's as if her demeanor totally changes.
Her stammering is completely gone, and she sounds like an expert.
Of course, that's not something you can be blamed for.
There are so many different skills and techniques that go into writing even a simple poem.
Not just finding them and building them, but getting them to work together is probably the most challenging part.
It might take you some time, but it all comes down with practice, and learning by example, and trying new things.
I also hope that everyone else in the club gives you valuable feedback.
Natsuki can be a little bit biased, though.
Biased?!
How?!
Um... well...
Never mind.
I shouldn't be talking about people like that.
Sorry.
It's fine!
I'm not sure if Yuri is apologizing to herself, to me, or to Natsuki.
Do you mind if I read your poem now?
Please do.
I'd love to share my thought process behind it.
Yuri smiles dreamily, as if that's a rare opportunity for her.
Which itself is kind of funny.
After all, isn't this supposed to be a literature club?
Yeah, right?
Ghost under the light.
The tendrils of my hair illuminate beneath the amber glow.
Bathing.
It must be this one.
The last remaining street light to have withstood the test of time.
The last yet to be replaced by the sickening blue-green hue of the future.
I bathe.
Calm breathing air of the present, but living in the past.
The light flickers.
I flicker back.
I really like this poem.
It's a good one.
I...
I'm sorry I have such terrible handwriting.
What?!
I wasn't thinking that at all!
But it took you a long time to read.
Ah!
Well, I just don't read script very often.
I actually think your handwriting is pretty!
Huh?
That's a relief.
Also...
I like the poem!
Even though it's short, it was really descriptive!
It wasn't too short.
I usually write longer poems.
Not at all!
I... I'm really glad you like it.
I'll be honest.
Since it's our first time sharing, I wanted to write something a little more... mild.
Something easy to digest, I suppose.
Are you into ghosts, Yuri?!
Huhu!
Actually, the story isn't about a ghost at all, Oliver!
Really?!
I must have totally missed the point!
Well, I suppose you did only glance over it after all.
But remember that poets often express their own thoughts, feelings, and experiences in their work.
They usually do more than tell a simple story or paint a picture.
In this case, perhaps the subject of the poem is only being symbolically compared to a ghost.
Lingering in her last remaining place of comfort, unable to let go of the past, and soon to be left with nothing.
That's a lot more solemn!
Putting it that way?!
I hadn't even thought of that!
That's impressive!
Huh?
It... it's nothing, really.
Yours was impressive, too, so...
Nah!
If anything, I could probably learn a thing or two from you!
You think so?
Yeah!
Of course!
Uh...
You know...
I was really nervous about doing all this.
But in the end, I enjoyed it.
I'm gonna keep doing my best for you, Oliver.
AHHHHH!
Me too!
Whoo!
I guess that's everyone.
I glance around the room.
That was a little more stressful than I anticipated.
It's as if everyone is judging me for my mediocre writing abilities!
Wait, something's wrong with the music.
Or... maybe not.
Even though they're just being nice, there's no way my poems can stand up to theirs.
This is a literature club, after all.
Ahh...
I guess that's what I ended up getting myself into.
Across the room, Monica is writing something in her notebook.
My eyes land on Yuri and Natsuki.
They gingerly exchange sheets of paper, sharing their respective poems.
As they read in tandem, I watch each of their expressions change.
Natsuki's eyebrows furrow in frustration.
Meanwhile, Yuri smiles sadly.
What's with this language?
Huh?
Um...
Did you say something?
Oh, it's nothing.
Natsuki dismissively returns to the poem...
Or returns the poem to the desk with one hand.
I guess you could say it's fancy.
Ah...
Thanks.
Yours is...
Cute.
Cute!
Did you completely miss the symbolism or something?
It's clearly about the feeling of giving up!
How could that be cute?
I... I know that.
I just meant...
The language, I guess.
I was trying to say something nice.
Eh?
You mean you have to try that hard to come up with something nice to say?
Thanks, but it really didn't come out nice at all!
Um...
Well, I do have a couple of suggestions.
Hmm.
If I was looking for suggestions, I would have asked someone who actually liked it.
Which people did, by the way!
Monica liked it.
And Oliver did too!
So based on that, I'll gladly give you some suggestions of my own.
First of all...
Excuse me.
I appreciate the offer, but I've spent a long time establishing my writing style.
I don't expect it to change anytime soon.
Unless, of course, I come across something particularly inspiring.
Which I haven't yet.
Mmm!
And Oliver liked my poem too, you know.
He even told me he was impressed by it.
Natsuki suddenly stands up.
Oh?
I didn't realize you were so invested in trying to impress our new member, Yuri!
Huh?
That's not what I...
Ooh...
You're...
You're just...
Yuri stands up as well!
Maybe you're just jealous that Oliver appreciates my advice more than he appreciated yours!
Huh?!
And how do you know he didn't appreciate my advice more?!
Are you that full of yourself?!
I...
No...
If I was full of myself...
I would deliberately go out of my way to make everything I do overly cutesy!
UGH!
Well, y-you know what?!
I wasn't the one whose boobs magically grew a size bigger as soon as Oliver started showing up!
N-Natsuki!
Um...
Natsuki, that's a little...
This doesn't involve you!
Taking out your own insecurities on others like that...
Did you really act as...
Lord, did you love Natsuki?!
Me?!
You wanna be edgy, bitch?!
Edgy?!
Sorry that my lifestyle is a little too wife for someone who met a late to comprehend!
Say it!
Just say anything that proves my point!
Most people often learn to get over themselves after they graduate middle school, you know?!
If you wanna prove anything, then stop harassing others with your sickening attitude!
You think you can counterbalance your toxic personality just by dressing and acting cute?!
The only cute thing about you is how hard you try!
Woah, be careful, Lord!
You might cut yourself on that ass, Yuri!
Oh my bad, you already do, don't you?
D-did you just accuse me of cutting myself?
What the fuck is wrong with your head?!
Yeah, go on!
Let Oliver hear everything you really think!
I'm sure he'll be head over heels for you after this!
Ah-ah!
Suddenly Yuri turns towards me!
As if she just noticed I was standing there!
Didn't Oliver!
She's just trying to make me look bad!
That's not true!
She started it!
That fucking Megan!
Wait...
What?
Hey Oliver?
Why don't we step outside for a little bit?
Okay?
Sorry about that!
They really shouldn't have tried to get you involved!
It's probably better for us to stay out of this!
We'll go back inside once they're done yelling!
Heh heh!
Some president I am, right?
I can't even confront my own club members properly!
What the fuck is going on in this game?!
But I never have it in me to put my foot down against others!
You understand, right?
Anyway...
If this makes you want to spend less time with the others, then that's fine!
I'd be happy to spend time with you instead!
Suddenly Natsuki runs out of the classroom!
She's already out of the classroom!
Oh wait, no, wait, never mind, that's Natsuki.
I keep mixing these girls up, man.
I guess she was crying.
She quickly runs away!
Oh dear.
Well, it looks like they're done!
Alright...
I didn't mean it...
Yuri is rocking back and forth in her desk, with her palms on her forehead.
Yuri?!
I didn't mean it!
I...
I believe you!
I have no idea what Yuri might have said to Natsuki!
Or did.
Oliver...
Please don't hate me.
Please.
I'm not like this.
There's something wrong with me today.
It's fine, Yuri.
We know you didn't mean it.
Besides, I'm sure Natsuki will forget all about it by tomorrow.
Completely.
Anyway, the meeting is over, so you can go home now if you want.
Yuri looks at me like she wants to say something.
But she keeps glancing at Monica.
Y- You can go first, Monica.
I'd like to stay a little bit longer.
I'm the president, so I should be the last one out.
I'll wait for you to be done.
Wait, she's trying to get in my pants now, too.
Well, I...
I'm VP, so...
Please let me take that responsibility today.
It kind of sounds like you don't want me around for something, Yuri.
It's not that.
I just...
I didn't get much of a chance to discuss my book with Oliver.
It would just be embarrassing with you listening.
I guess I don't really have a choice, do I?
I'm sorry for causing trouble.
But I really appreciate it in Kyrgyzstan!
What the fuck?
We're going, Yuri.
It's Eternity.
20 out of 20, baby!
You ready?
It's gonna be empty.
Speed run!
Uh...
I, uh...
Fuck, this one's hard.
Time!
Um, let's do...
Oh, man.
Uh...
Man, this one's tough!
I don't know!
Kawaii?!
Fuck!
I don't know what that means!
I already fucked it up!
Oh my god...
Whatever!
At this point, I have nothing to live for.
Ambient.
Intellectual.
Headphone...
Oh, that's her?!
Okay, good to know.
Uh...
Disarray.
Philosophy.
Uh, amazing.
Ah!
Damn it!
Defeat.
Okay, good.
After image.
Okay, nice!
Let's do...
Uh, Infallible?
Nice!
Contamination.
Yes!
Question!
Uh...
Death.
Yeah!
Infinite.
Uh...
Special, maybe?
Oh no!
Parfait!
Oh!
This was a horrible one.
But I also tried to speedrun, so, you know, I messed it up.
That was on me.
I hope I got more Yuri than I got...
Uh...
What's her name?
Monica.
And why are there only two girls in that?
Shouldn't there be three?
It's so confusing.
Another day passes, and it's time for the club meeting already.
I've gotten a little more comfortable here over the past couple days.
Entering the club room, the usual scene greets me.
Welcome back, Oliver.
Ha!
Hi, Yuri!
I'm not sure if it's me, or if it's Yuri's expression.
But the weight of yesterday's quarrel still hangs in the air a little.
Um...
Yuri glances over her shoulder, looking around the room.
Natsuki is reading manga at a desk.
And surprisingly, Monica isn't here yet.
Suddenly, Yuri takes my arm and pulls me to the corner of the room, oh shit!
About yesterday...
I...
I really need to apologize.
Nothing like that has ever happened before.
And something just came over me, I guess.
I wasn't acting mentally sound.
Please don't think we're usually like this.
Not just me, but Natsuki as well.
Yuri!
I'm happy that you were considerate and apologized!
You don't have to worry too much!
Even though I've only been here a couple days!
I could tell something was off yesterday!
Maybe...
See?
Ah, it's gonna kill me!
Fucking funny.
Ah!
Alright.
Phew!
Maybe...
Oh, no way.
No way.
Brickhandle!
But whatever it was...
It didn't make me think any less of you!
I had already decided that there's no way you can be a bad person!
And now that you're apologizing, I know you really didn't mean it!
Ah...
Oliver...
Don't say those kinds of things so frankly.
They make me a little too happy.
I'm really glad that you're such an understanding person.
And I'm really glad that you joined this club.
Everything is a little bit brighter with you around.
And...
Ah...
Sorry, what am I saying right now?
I just...
Hey, have you guys seen Monica?
Ah!
No, I haven't!
I was also kinda wondering where she was!
Man!
Yuri, I'm guessing you haven't either!
Yuri is clearly taken aback by how calmly Natsuki is addressing her.
No, I haven't.
Jeez, this isn't like her at all!
I know it's stupid, but I can't help but worry a little bit.
What?
Why are you looking at me like that?
Um...
Natsuki...
About yesterday...
I... I... I just wanted to apologize.
I promise I didn't mean any of the things that I... I... I said.
And I'll do my best to stay under control from now on.
So?
Yuri...
What the heck are you talking about?
Did you do something yesterday?
Huh?
Jeez...
What was on your mind, I'm sure it was nothing.
I don't even remember anything bad happening.
You're the kind of person who worries too much about the little things, aren't you?
But... but...
Me pulls out a cloud blindside lifeline anal respectability!
I'll accept your apology anyway if it helps you feel better about it.
Besides, it's kind of nice to hear since I was always afraid you secretly hated me or something like that.
Eh-heh!
No!
N-not at all.
I don't hate you.
Eh-heh!
Well, you're kind of weird, but I don't hate you either.
Natsuki turns to me.
You're still on trial, though.
Hey!
Suddenly, the door swings open.
Sorry!
I'm super sorry.
Ha!
There you are!
I didn't mean to be late.
I hope you guys weren't worried or anything.
Naaaaa!
Well, Natsuki was!
I-I was not!
Eh-heh!
What took you so long, anyway?
Um...
Well, my last period today was study hall.
Oh, I... thought something else at the start of that sentence.
To be honest, I kind of just lost track of time.
Eh-heh!
That makes no sense, though!
You would've heard the bell ring, at least!
I-I must not have heard it since I was practicing piano!
Piano?
I wasn't aware you played music at all, Monica.
Ah, don't give me more credit than I deserve!
I guess I've been practicing it for a while, but I'm still not really good yet.
Still...
That must require a lot of dedication.
So I'm still impressed.
Ah-heh!
Well, thanks, Yuri!
You should play something for us sometime!
Ah-heh, that's...
Monica looks at me!
Well, I'm working on writing a song, but it's not quite done yet.
Maybe once I get a little bit better, I will.
That sounds cool!
I look forward to it!
Is that so?
In that case, I won't let you down, Oliver.
Monica smiles sweetly and stands in an awkward posture.
Ah!
I didn't mean any pressure or anything like that!
Haha, don't worry.
I was hoping that I could share it with you anyway.
I guess that's why I've been practicing so much recently.
I see!
I'm not sure if Monica was referring to the whole club or just me.
In that case, best of luck!
Thanks!
So, I didn't miss anything, did I?
No!
Not really!
I choose not to bring up anything that the three of us talked about.
Besides, Natsuki has already run off into the closet.
What?
Yuri... I mean, Oliver...
Um...
Since your compliments put me in a good mood, I was wondering if you would like to spend some time together today?
I mean, in the club?
Yeah!
Definitely!
I planned on it anyway!
Okay.
Can we start now?
Let's find a place to sit.
Ah!
I'm being a little forceful, aren't I?
I'm sorry.
My heart just won't stop pounding for some reason.
Don't worry about it!
If anything...
If anything, it's nice to see you have so much energy!
Yeah.
But...
I need to try to calm down.
I won't be able to focus on reading like this.
This music is gonna fucking drive me to the crazy world.
Take your time!
Yuri takes a deep breath and pulls a copy of the book out of her back.
Actually, I have a request.
Do you mind if I make some tea first?
Not at all!
Go for it!
Thanks very much.
If there's one thing that can make my reading time here any better, it's a nice cup of tea.
Not to mention for yourself as well.
Yuri stands up and makes her way to the closet.
I follow and watch as she retrieves a small water pitcher from the shelf.
The kind with a filter inside.
For a second I thought it was gonna say the kind with water inside.
Can you hold this for a second?
Sure!
Yuri heads me the water pitcher and also fetches an electric kettle!
I'm gonna pluck this in at the teacher's desk.
And then I'll go get some water.
She walks past me and sets the kettle down on the teacher's desk.
I simply watch her movements.
To my surprise, the way she moves really contrasts her speaking mannerisms.
What does that even mean?
Especially because of her long legs, Yuri appears elegant and methodical.
Okay, may I have the water pitcher?
Thanks, I'll be right back.
Ah!
I might as well walk with you!
Th-that's okay.
You stay here.
It won't take long.
Pitcher in hand, Yuri hurries out of the classroom.
Ah!
Did Yuri leave you again?
No, it's not like that this time!
She's just filling up the water pitcher to make tea!
Oh.
Okay.
Sorry for misunderstanding.
Whatever, Monika.
Bye, Monika!
Ten minutes pass.
Yuri said it wouldn't take that long.
Is something holding her up?
Oh my god, hopefully she didn't leave with a knife.
I'm bored just waiting here, so I decided to go look for her.
Let's see.
The most logical place for Yuri to be would be...
nearest the water fountain.
I start heading down the hallway.
Ahhhh!
What's that noise?
It's coming from around the corner!
It sounds like breathing!
A sharp inhale!
Like someone is sucking the air through their teeth!
Are they in pain?
I reach the corner and peer around it!
Yuri!
Kya!
I'm bored!
I'm back!
Thanks for waiting patiently!
Oliver, do you like oolong tea?
Oh yeah!
Anything is fine!
Very well.
Yuri sets the temperature on the kettle to 200 degrees.
Now it's time to get the teapot.
You really do this properly, don't you?
Of course.
I shouldn't do any less when I'm making tea for others.
Even if I'm not an expert on tea or anything?
In that case you'll be...
even more impressed.
Ha!
Perhaps I will!
Yuri fetches the teapot.
And begins measuring the tea leaves.
How do you measure tea leaves?
That makes no sense.
To my surprise, she even starts humming a little to herself.
You must be in a good mood now!
Is that so?
I was letting it show.
And you noticed.
I was doing a bit of thinking.
And I decided that I would try expressing myself a little bit more.
It turns out that it's not very hard for me to do.
When it's you who's around anyway.
Ah!
That's great, Yuri!
Just don't push yourself too much!
You're always worrying about me, Oliver.
It's very endearing.
That's...
Yuri wasn't kidding.
I don't even know if I can keep up with this.
I watched Yuri pour a cup of tea for each of us.
Oliver, I have another request.
Do you mind if we sit on the floor today?
Huh?
Why's that?
It's a little bit easier on my back.
I can read with my back against the wall rather than bending over at my desk.
Ah!
Sorry, I didn't realize!
No worries.
I just have back pain fairly regularly.
So I do my best to manage it.
Is that so?
I wonder why that is.
It's most likely because my...
Ah!
My...
Your posture, right?!
Always hunched over like that while we're reading!
Yes!
I have terrible reading posture, that's it.
So that's why we should sit on the floor.
Fair enough!
I'll go ahead and get the book!
I retrieve the book from my bag.
Ah!
I have some chocolate as well!
Oh, here we go!
It's a bag of small chocolate candies.
Chocolate candy?
I take it, since it'll go well with the tea.
Yuri and I then sit against the wall, tea cups at our sides.
As if in sync, we assume the same reading position as last time, each holding one half of the book.
Wait a minute!
Oh, I thought they were referencing the last last time.
Except this time...
Our bodies are even closer to each other.
I can't see too well.
Yuri slides closer until our shoulders are touching.
How am I supposed to focus on reading like this?!
Yuri was always kinda cute, but...
When she's being less apprehensive, it's almost more than I can handle!
Your teacup!
Yuri hands me my teacup.
Holding it with my hand that's not holding the book, I end up in a position that makes it even harder to focus.
Because now I need to worry about making sure I don't accidentally touch her chest.
Meanwhile, Yuri hasn't noticed a single thing.
She wears her intense reading expression, and I can only presume the world around her has faded away.
I use all of my willpower to focus on reading.
After a few minutes, I finally manage to relax a little.
I put the teacup between my legs, and fumble with the chocolate wrapper.
Ha!
Sorry!
I briefly let go of the book to finish opening the wrapper.
You can have as much as you want!
Ah, that's...
That's okay, I won't take any.
Huh?!
Are you sure?!
Well...
If I touch it, then it might get smudges on the pages?
Ah, you're right!
I didn't even think about that!
My bad.
No need to apologize.
I'll hold the book, okay?
Are you sure?!
Of course.
Oh, here we go!
Yuri opens the book with both hands!
Are her eyelids bleeding?
The fuck is going on there?
She holds it so that I don't have any harder of a time reading from it.
But as a result, her left arm is practically resting on top of my leg!
Well, in that case...
Yuri is already totally focused on reading again.
I take a chocolate candy and pop it into my mouth.
Then, I take another chocolate...
And I hold it up to Yuri.
She doesn't even look away from the book.
She simply parts her lips...
As if this situation was completely natural.
But that means I can't stop here!
I apprehensively place the chocolate in her mouth!
Just like that, Yuri closes her lips over it.
Huh?
Yuri's expression suddenly breaks.
It...
Did I just...
Yuri looks at me like she needs to confirm what just happened.
Um...
Oliver...
Sorry!
I guess I shouldn't have done that!
Yuri starts to breathe heavily...
I...
I can't...
Oliver...
Suddenly Yuri forcefully grabs my arm...
And jerks me to my feet!
My teacup gets knocked over.
Oliver!
My heart...
My heart won't stop pounding, Oliver!
I can't calm down.
I can't focus on anything anymore.
Can you feel it, Oliver?
Yuri suddenly presses my hand against her chest.
Why is this happening to me?
I feel like I'm losing my mind.
I can't...
I can't make it stop.
It even makes me not wanna read.
I just want...
To look...
At you...
Uh...
Yeah...
Time to leave!
It's time to share poems!
Fuckin' hell safe by the bell.
Monica!
Oliver, I think you saw something earlier that you weren't supposed to see.
I didn't wanna have to tell you this, but...
I don't think I have a choice.
It's getting kinda dangerous for you to spend so much time with Yuri.
I don't know why, but she seems pretty easily excitable when she's around you.
You do know why.
It shouldn't be a problem in itself.
Dude, Yuri wants to cut off my limbs!
She wants to kill me!
But when Yuri gets too excited, she finds a place to hide and starts cutting herself with a pocket knife.
Holy shit, you just say that out loud like that.
Isn't that kinda messed up?
She even brings a different note to school every day.
Or a different one.
Like, she has a collection or something.
I mean, it's definitely not because she's depressed or anything like that.
Oh yeah, why is it then?
I think she just gets some kind of high from it.
Oh my god, she's a freak!
It might even be like...
A sexual thing.
But the point is, you've been kind of enabling her.
I'm not saying it's your fault though.
But I guess that's why I had to explain it all to you.
So, I think if you keep your distance, that would probably be best for her.
While you're at it, don't be shy to spend a little more time with me.
To put it lightly, I at least have it together in the head.
And I know how to treat my club members.
But anyway...
You wanna read my poem now?
I like the way this one turned out, so I hope you do too.
Okay, save me.
The colors they want.
Bright, beautiful colors.
Flashing...
Pearson...
Red, green, blue.
Endless...
Cacophony of meaningless noise.
The noise it won't stop!
Violent...
Grating...
rooms.
Sequence, screech, screech, piercing, sine, cosine, tangent.
Like playing chalkboard on a table.
Like playing a knife on a breathing ribcage.
Endless poem of meaningless...
The leader.
Man, you are...
Sorry, what did you just say?
You said you weren't singing that?
Sorry, I know it's kind of abstract.
I'm just trying to, um...
Well, never mind.
There's no point in explaining.
Anyway...
Here's Monica's writing tip of the day!
Sometimes you'll find yourself facing a difficult decision.
When that happens, don't forget to save your game!
You're right.
True shit.
Done.
You never know when, um...
Who am I talking to?
Can you hear me?
Tell me you can hear me!
Anything!
Please help me.
Okay.
That's my advice for today!
Thanks for listening.
Dude, we're all trapped in a simulation.
They're trying to get out!
Uh, let's do...
Natsuki.
Well, I can admit that it's better than the last one.
It's nice to see that you're putting in some effort.
That's good!
Just make sure you find a little bit of influence from everyone.
I think you're at least being influenced by Yuri a little bit, aren't you?
I mean, I know you've been, like...
Spending some time with her or whatever.
But you know, Monica and I are just as good as her.
At poems, I mean.
So you should really try to learn something or you'll never get better.
Here's the one I wrote.
I'll make sure you learn something from it.
Amy likes spiders!
You know what I heard about Amy?
Amy likes spiders.
Icky, wriggly, hairy, ugly spiders.
Fuck Amy.
That's why I'm not friends with her.
Exactly!
Amy has a cute singing voice.
I heard her singing my favorite love song.
Every time she sang the chorus, my heart would pound to the rhythm of the words.
But she likes spiders.
That's why I'm not friends with her.
One time, I hurt my leg really bad.
Amy helped me up and took me to the nurse.
I tried not to let her touch me.
She likes spiders, so her hands are probably gross.
That's why I'm not friends with her.
Amy has a lot of friends.
I always see her talking to people.
She probably talks about spiders.
What if her friends start to like spiders too?
That's why I'm not friends with her.
It doesn't matter if she has other hobbies.
It doesn't matter if she keeps it private.
It doesn't matter if it doesn't hurt anyone.
It's gross.
She's gross.
The world is better off without spider lovers.
And I'm gonna tell everyone.
This is...
Natsuki, you need help.
Not bad, right?
It's quite a bit longer than yesterday's.
Yesterday's was way too short.
I was just warming up.
Hope you didn't think that was the best I could do.
No, of course not.
Anyway, the message is pretty straightforward in this poem.
I doubt I have to explain it.
Like anyone would agree that the subject of this poem is an ignorant jerk.
Everyone has some kind of weird hobby or a guilty pleasure.
Something that you're afraid if people find out that make fun of you or think less of you.
But that just makes people stupid.
Who cares what someone likes as long as they're not hurting anyone and it makes them happy?
I think people really need to learn to respect others for liking weird things.
Such as two of the girls in this very club, whom I respectfully won't name.
Kind of ironic that even in my one place of comfort I can even have people respect me.
Geez, now you're making me complain too much.
What did I do?
For what it's worth, I respect you!
Well, I guess thanks.
But it's kind of obvious that you'll respect Yuri more, so...
Whatever.
We're done sharing, so you can leave now.
Alright.
Who should I show my poem to next?
How about Yuri?
I've been waiting for this.
Let's see what you've written for today.
Yuri stares at the poem with a surprised expression on her face.
Do you like it?
Oliver...
This one might even be better than yesterday's.
How did you even pick up on this so quickly?
Just yesterday I was telling you the kind of techniques worth practicing.
Maybe that's why!
You did a good job explaining!
I really wanted to try giving it more imagery!
Yuri visibly swallows.
Even her hands appear sweaty.
Ah...
That makes me so happy!
It's so amazing to feel like I'm valued, Oliver!
Everything that you write is a treasure to me.
My heart pounds just holding it!
I wanna write a poem about this feeling.
Is that bad, Oliver?
I'm not being weird, right?
I...
I'm having a harder time than usual at concealing my emotions.
I'm kind of embarrassed.
But right now I just want you to read my poem too.
Okay?
Wheel!
A rotating wheel.
Turning an axle.
Grinding.
Bolted.
Linear gearbox.
Falling sky.
Seven holy stakes.
A docked ship.
A postal to another world.
A thin rope tied to a thick rope.
A torn harness.
Parabolic gearbox.
Expanding universe.
Time controlled by slipping cogwheels.
Existence of God.
Swimming with open water in all directions.
Drowning.
A prayer written in blood.
A prayer written in time-devouring snakes with human eyes.
A threat connecting all living human eyes.
A kaleidoscope of holy stakes.
Exponential gearbox.
A sky of exploding stars.
God disproving the existence of God.
A wheel rotating in six dimensions.
Forty gears and a ticking clock.
A clock that ticks one second for every rotation of the planet.
A clock that ticks forty times every time it ticks every second time.
A bolt head of holy stakes tied to the existence of a dark ship to another world.
A kaleidoscope of blood written in clocks.
A time-devouring prayer connecting a sky of forty gears and open human eyes in all directions.
Breathing gearbox.
Breathing bolt head.
Breathing ship.
Breathing postal.
Breathing snakes.
Breathing God.
Breathing blood.
Breathing holy stakes.
Breathing human eyes.
Breathing time.
Breathing prayer sky real.
Oh!
It doesn't really matter what it's about.
My mind has been a little hyperactive lately, so I had to take it out on your pen.
That is... A pen fell out of your backpack yesterday, so I took it home for safekeeping, and... I, um... I just really like the way that it writes.
So I wrote this... poem with it.
And now you're touching it.
I am okay.
Why did I just... Can we pretend this conversation never happened?
You can keep the poem, though?
Fucking freak!
Yes, read it.
Today I cut my skin open for the first time.
It was exhilarating.
I think I understand how... feels now.
I'm supposed to be the responsible one.
So I don't think I'll be doing it again, unless I decide to kill myself.
I left the memento of the occasion below.
Okay, everyone!
We're all done reading each other's poems, right?
We have something we need to go over today.
So if everyone could come sit at the front of the room...
Is this about the festival?
Well, sort of.
Ugh!
Do we really have to do something for the festival?
It's not like we can put together anything good in just a few days.
We'll just end up embarrassing ourselves instead of getting any new members.
That's a concern of mine as well.
I don't really do well with last-minute preparations.
Don't worry so much!
We're gonna keep it simple, okay?
Look, I know everyone's here a little more lively ever since Oliver joined and we've started with some club activities.
But this isn't the time for us to become complacent.
We still only have four members.
And the festival is our only real chance to find more, you know?
What's so great about getting new members anyway?
We already have enough to be considered an official club.
More members will just mean everything gets noisier and more difficult to manage.
Natsuki, I don't think you're looking at it the right way at all.
Don't you want to share your passion with as many people as you can?
To inspire them to find the same feelings that brought you here in the first place?
The literature club should be a place where people can express themselves like they can't do anywhere else.
It should be a place so intimate that you never want to leave.
I know you feel that way, too.
I know we all do.
So that's why we should work hard!
And put something together for the festival.
Even if it's something small.
Right, Oliver?
Ahhhhhhh!
Oh, come on!
You can't take advantage of Oliver to agree with you just because he doesn't know how to say no to anything.
Look, Monica.
Do you really think any of us here joined the club with other people in mind?
Yuri never even talked until Oliver joined.
As for me, I just like it better here than I do at home.
And Oliver isn't even passionate about literature in the first place.
And that's everyone.
Sorry, but you're really the only one who's so interested in finding new members.
The rest of us are fine like this.
I know you're precedent and all, but you should really consider our options for once.
Monica is clearly taken aback by Natsuki's words.
That's... not true at all!
I'm sure Yuri and Oliver want to get more members too.
Right?
I don't know about Yuri, but I'm kind of indifferent.
If I showed as much enthusiasm as Monica wanted, then I'd probably be lying.
Still, if it's up to me to rescue this situation...
Um...
No.
Natsuki's right, isn't she?
This club...
It's nothing more than a place for a few people to hang out.
Why did I think that everyone here saw it the same way as I did?
But that doesn't mean that we're against getting new members or anything!
Oliver, why did you even join this club?
What were you hoping to get out of it?
Well?
That's not really something I can be honest about, is it?
In fact...
If I remember, you weren't even given a choice not to join!
Monica sits down and stares at her desk.
What's the point of all this anyway?
What if starting this club was a mistake?
Now you've done it, Natsuki.
What, me?
I just broke my mind!
Is it a crime to be honest?
It's not about being honest.
It's about word choice.
Besides, you have no right to speak for everyone else in the club like that.
You don't understand at all!
I just...
I just want a place that feels nice to hang out with a few friends.
Is there a problem with the club being that for me?
There aren't...
There aren't many other places like that for me.
And now Monica wants to take it away from me.
She's not taking anything away!
No, Oliver.
It's not the same.
It won't be the same with the direction she wants to take it.
If I wanted that, then I could have just joined any other stupid club.
But this one...
I mean...
At least for a little bit of time...
Things were nice!
Natsuki starts packing up her things.
I'm going home!
I feel like I don't belong here right now.
Natsuki...
Natsuki ignores Yuri and walks right out of the classroom.
This is bad.
I don't know what to do.
Well?
You have an opinion on the festival!
I... I don't know.
I'm kind of indifferent, I guess.
Who cares about the obnoxious brandy?
I mean, I like how nice and quiet the club is right now.
And I'm just...
Happy with you here.
But still...
I'm the vice president.
It's not right for me to ignore my responsibilities like that.
Nobody would cry if she killed herself!
I should do my best to consider everyone's perspective and make the decision that's right for the club.
But what about you, Oliver?
What do you want to get out of this club?
Yuri repeats the same question as Monica.
I decide giving an indirect answer is better than nothing.
I... I think the most important thing is for everyone to get along!
And for the club to provide something that you can't get anywhere else!
I don't think it's about how many members, but rather the quality of each new member!
That's what will end up making the Literature Club a special place!
I see.
I really agree with you.
Each member contributes their own qualities in a... special way.
With each change in members, the identity of the club as a whole will change, too.
I don't think that's necessarily a bad thing.
Step out of your comfort zone once in a while.
So if you would like to help Monica with the festival, then I'm on your side as well.
All right!
Well, maybe we can all talk to Natsuki tomorrow!
Yuri nods.
Hey, Yuri!
Huh?
Um, I know things were a little awkward yesterday.
But I feel like you deserve to know that I still think you're a wonderful vice president.
And also a wonderful friend.
M-Monica...
I wanna do everything I can to make this the best club ever!
Okay?
Me too.
Yeah!
Let's all go home for today.
We'll talk about the festival tomorrow.
Okay.
I look forward to it.
Shall we go, Oliver?
Um...
Please don't take this the wrong way, but...
I'm gonna chat a little bit with Oliver before we leave.
Just to see what he thinks of this time here and all that.
It's important to me as president.
Yuri looks a little troubled, but she doesn't protest.
Okay.
I trust your judgment, Monica.
In that case, I'll see the two of you tomorrow.
See you tomorrow!
Monica waves as Yuri exits the classroom.
Phew!
Things have been a bit hectic lately, haven't they?
Oliver, I just wanted to make sure you're not...
Or that you're enjoying your time in this club.
I would really hate to see you unhappy.
I feel kinda like I'm responsible for that.
As president.
And I really do care about you, you know?
I don't like seeing the other girls give you a hard time.
With how mean Natsuki is and everything.
And Yuri being a little bit...
You know...
Sometimes it feels like you and I are the only real people here.
You know what I mean?
But it's weird, because in all the time you've been here, we've hardly gotten to spend any time together.
I mean...
I guess it's technically only been a couple days.
Sorry, I didn't mean to say something weird.
There are just some things I've been hoping to talk about with you.
Things I know only you could understand.
That's right, no, no, wait.
Wait, what?
Huh?
I wasn't clicking!
Okay, 2020, baby.
Here we go, you ready?
I'm gonna...
Oh my god, that's it.
Here we go!
Okay, let's see.
It's gotta be...
Scars, I guess?
Yes!
Entropy.
Wait, what?!
Wait, wait.
111 out of 20?!
After image.
Ambient.
Yes!
Philosophy?
This time, though.
I don't know.
Maybe...
Hope?
Oh my god, really?
Okay.
Dark.
Um...
It's not that one!
Unending.
Yes!
Electricity?
Eternity.
And...
Intellectual?
Nice!
Wait, what's happening up here?!
I guess if you add them all up.
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10, 11, 12, 13.
Let's do...
Uh...
Melancholy.
Nice!
Universe!
What?!
No way!
That was Yuri!
Bullshit stealing my words.
I don't believe it.
Let's do...
Daydream?
Yes!
Massacre!
What about...
Inferno?
No.
Uh...
Tears.
Yeah!
Disarray?
I'm so good.
Starscape?
Oh god, I don't know.
Uh...
Oh god.
Let's do...
Uh...
Fuck, this is a hard one!
I can't...
I don't know.
Milk?
No!
Fuck!
I will never get it.
I'll never get it.
Oh my god.
World Wind.
Lovely.
That was a lovely drawing.
I've been waiting for you.
Are you ready to continue reading?
I brought my best tea today.
Monika!
I told you not to...
Ugh!
Is she really late again?
Inconsiderate as usual, Natsuki.
Excuse me?
Must you always interrupt my conversations with your incessant yelling?
What are you talking about?
You say that like I do it on a regular basis or something.
I just wasn't paying attention, okay?
I'm sorry.
Seriously, what's gotten into you lately?
Me?
Nothing.
Is it really that bad?
See, it is something!
I'll get over it.
It's not even anything noteworthy.
I've just been feeling a little unedged lately.
Anyway, we don't need to talk about it.
Well, I just feel like I need to bring it up.
It's not like I really care or anything.
Oh, man!
I'm the last one here again!
Well, Oliver just walked in too.
Were you practicing piano again?
Yeah!
You must have a lot of determination.
Starting this club and still trying to make time for piano?
Well, maybe not determination, but I guess passion.
It motivates me to work hard for the festival and...
Um...
Right!
I forgot.
About that, Natsuki.
We were all talking yesterday and...
Well, we decided that we would like to support the festival as well.
However, I understand how you feel about not wanting the club to change.
I think we all kind of feel that way.
So as long as we're all working together, this club will never become something we don't want.
Um...
Also...
If you help us out with the festival...
Then I'll buy you a new manga!
Ahaha!
Sorry, that last part was really funny.
Look!
I did some thinking about yesterday.
I was a little more hostile than I meant to be.
I guess I really felt threatened or something.
But I know this is something we're doing together.
Another new member wouldn't hurt as long as they're cool.
And I guess another girl would be nice this time.
But more importantly, I would hate to see the event just suck because I chose to back out!
I'm a pro, you know!
So I'm gonna help too!
And make sure it's done right!
Thank goodness.
Isn't that great, Monica?
Monica?
Ah!
Yeah!
That's wonderful!
It wouldn't be the same without you, Natsuki.
Anyway, Oliver!
What do you want to do today?
I was thinking we could...
We already have plans today.
Huh?
Is that so, Yuri?
That's correct.
Oliver is already engaged in a novel that we're reading together.
Aren't you glad that I've already gotten him into literature, Monica?
I...
I suppose...
I was just...
Actually, it doesn't matter.
It really doesn't.
You guys can do whatever you want.
Yes!
Um, thank you for understanding, Monica.
Ha ha ha!
Actually, I have a request.
Do you mind if I make some tea first?
I do, in fact!
Fuck your tea!
Not at all!
Thanks very much.
If there's one thing that can make my reading time here any better, it's a nice cup of tea.
Oh, yeah?
Not to mention for yourself as well.
Yuri stands up and makes her way to the closet.
Wait, closet?
I follow and watch as she retrieves a small water pitcher from the shelf.
The kind with water inside.
Can you hold this for a second?
Sure!
Yuri hands me the water pitcher and also pitches an electric kettle.
I'm gonna plug this into the teacher's desk.
And then I'll go get some water.
She wa- I'm fu- Dude, this game is frying me.
I think I'm losing brain cells reading this.
I'm... this is just...
I... yeah...
She walks past me and sets the kettle down on the teacher's desk.
I simply watch her movements, like a creep.
To my surprise, the way she moves really contrasts her speaking mannerisms.
Especially because of her long legs, Yuri appears to float.
Okay, may I have the water pitcher?
Thanks, I'll be right back.
Ha!
I might as well walk with you!
Th- that's okay.
You- you stay here.
It won't take long.
Pitcher in hand, Yuri hurries out of the classroom.
Ah!
Did Yuri leave you again?
No, it's not like that this time!
She's just filling up the water pitcher to make tea!
Ah, okay.
Sorry for misunderstanding.
Trying to look for any opening she can.
Ten minutes pass.
Yuri said it wouldn't take long.
Is something holding her up?
I'm bored just waiting here so I decide to go look for her.
Why are we doing this again?!
Let's see.
The most logical place for Yuri to be would be the nearest water fountain.
I start heading down the hallway.
What's that noise?!
It's coming from around the corner!
It sounds like breathing!
A sharp inhale.
Like someone is sucking the air through their teeth.
Are they in pain?
I reach the corner and peer around it.
Yuri?!
Gah!
Oh my god!
How did I...
Sorry, I just had a really weird day shovel.
Me too!
This hasn't happened before anything, right?
My head's been a little fuzzy lately.
I hope it hasn't really been showing or anything.
I would hate for you to think I'm just weird after we started spending time together.
I mean...
Everyone has a few unusual things about them.
But expressing those things so soon after meeting someone is usually seen as inappropriate.
Or unlikable.
At least that's what I've discovered.
When I was a bit younger I think I would come on really strongly and get a little too intense.
It made people not want to be around me.
So I started hating those things about myself.
My obsession with certain hobbies.
And the way I can't control myself when I get too excited about something.
So...
I eventually stopped trying to talk to people.
If nobody could ever like me for the things that matter most to me.
Then it's just easier if I close myself off.
But recently something's been wrong.
I don't know what it is.
But every time we come to the club my heart starts to go crazy.
Like it's gonna rip out of my chest.
It overwhelms me with energy and emotions that I can't let out.
It's been making me do weird things.
I don't know why it's happening.
Oliver...
Is it just me?
Or has Monica been acting a little off lately?
She's always been a sweetheart ever since I joined the club.
But recently I've been feeling something sharp whenever she's around.
I'm not crazy right?
Please tell me I'm not.
I couldn't say anything before because she's always listening.
But finally...
We're alone!
Can we just stay here for a while?
Yeah.
I just wanna stay here.
Just the two of us.
We can stay here until the club ends.
And then we'll have the club room all to ourselves.
Nobody twins of fear with our...
Reading time.
Nobody to make me feel like stabbing myself in the throat.
Ah!
That was a joke!
That's a joke!
I don't like knives though.
Someone's fading in.
They sound strange but you wouldn't understand it.
You've never seen how beautiful they can be.
I have an idea.
Why don't you come to my house sometime?
I can show you my collection.
I've gotten them all from various artisans.
I make sure to give them all their fair share of use.
I don't want them to get lonely or anything.
Nobody deserves to be lonely.
Nobody.
And that's why I'm so happy you joined the literature club, Oliver.
Now we don't need to be lonely anymore.
Because we have each other.
Every day.
That's all we need.
You know what?
Let's quit the literature club.
There's no need for us to be around Monica's slimy tongue anymore.
Not to mention that other pathetic child.
We can walk home together every day after school.
And read together.
Eat together.
Sleep together.
Doesn't that sound perfect?
It's everything we could ever want.
Isn't that why you joined the club in the first place?
It's almost like it was fate.
Fate that would...
Meet each other.
What the fuck is this?
Is that Sayori?
And now we get the happy ending that I've patiently awaited years for.
Will you do that with me, Oliver?
Will n'yakshn'yabra-sa-a-a-a-shn'y.
Natsuki!
Fucking weirdos.
Meh.
I guess you really haven't learned anything after all.
Honestly, I don't know why I got my hopes up in the first place.
This is clearly Yuri's influence.
I didn't realize you were so impressionable.
Spending all this time with her in the club.
Now trying to ride like her.
This is stupid.
At least Monica appreciates my riding.
Ugh!
Okay.
Oliver, I guess I'm gonna have to share my poem with you now.
I really hate that I have to do this.
But unfortunately, I don't have much of a choice.
Just... read it carefully.
Okay?
And you can go away.
I don't know how else to bring this up.
But there's been something I've been worried about.
Yuri has been acting kind of strange lately.
You've only been here a few days.
So you may not know what I mean.
But she's not normally like this.
She's always been quiet and polite and attentive.
Things like that.
Okay.
This is really embarrassing.
But I'm forcing myself to suck it up.
The truth is, I'm really worried about her.
But if I try talking to her, she'll just get mad at me again.
I don't know what to do.
I think you're the only person that she'll listen to.
I don't know why.
But please try to do something.
Maybe you can convince her to talk to a therapist.
I've always wanted to bring better friends with Yuri.
And it really hurts me to see this happening.
I know I'm not gonna hate myself later for admitting that.
But right now, I don't care.
I just feel so hopeless.
Helpless.
So please see if you can do something to help.
I don't want anything bad to happen to her.
I'll make you cupcakes if I have to.
Just please try to do something.
As for Monika, I don't know why, but she's been really dismissive about this.
It's like she just wants us to ignore it.
So I'm mad at her right now.
And that's why I'm coming to you about this.
Don't let her know I wrote this.
Just pretend like I gave you a really good poem, okay?
I'm counting on you.
Thanks for reading.
That's just my mind!
Ignore everything you just read.
There's no point in trying to do anything.
It's Yuri's own fault that she's so unlikable.
Can you hear me, Oliver?
If you would just spend some time with Monika, all these problems would go away.
Yuri and I are too messed up for someone as wonderful as you.
Just think of Monika from now on.
Just Monika.
Monika.
Just Monika!
Monika!
No!
We're going with Yuri!
Who should I show my poem to next?
Yuri!
Finally.
Yuri holds my poem to her face and takes a deep breath.
I love it.
I love everything about it.
Oliver, I want to take this home.
Will you let me keep it?
Please?
Sure!
I don't care!
You're too nice to Oliver.
I've never met anyone as nice as you.
I could die.
No, not really, but...
I just don't know how to describe it.
It's okay to be feeling this way, right?
It's not bad, right?
Yuri holds my poem to her chest.
I'm gonna take this home with me.
And keep it in my room.
I hope that it makes you feel good when you think about me having it.
I'll take good care of it.
I'll even touch myself while really reading it over and over.
I'll give myself paper cuts so your skin oil enters my bloodstream.
You can have my poem too.
Besides, after you read it, I know you're really gonna wanna keep it.
Here, take it.
I can't wait any longer.
Hurry, read it!
Yeah, okay.
Do you like it?
I wrote it for you.
In case you couldn't tell, the poem is...
More importantly, I'm endowed it with my scent.
See, aren't I the most thoughtful person in the club?
I...
I think I'm gonna vomit.
Alright, let's show it to Monica.
Don't say I didn't warn you, Oliver!
I guess you...
No.
I can't convince myself to go to therapy when I'm the happiest I've ever been.
I'd rather keep this up until I blow my cover and someone takes me to the emergency room.
That's fucking dark.
It's time to figure out the festival preparations!
Let's hurry and get this over with!
Jeez!
Why is the mood so weird today?
Look, even Yuri isn't immune to it!
Ugh...
Stagnating air is...
Common foreshadowing that something terrible is about to happen...
Look!
Can we just get this done?
I'm gonna be printing and assembling all the poetry pamphlets.
Natsuki, I was thinking.
I wanna make cupcakes!
Yeah, that.
Glad we're on the same page.
Yuri, you can...
Well, it doesn't matter.
Do whatever you want, as long as you think it'll help.
Monica!
I'm not useless, you know.
I know that!
I already know what I'd like to do.
We can't run a successful poetry event without having the right atmosphere for the occasion.
So I'm gonna make... decorations.
And set up some nice mood lighting.
There, see?
That's a great idea.
And that gives us all something to do.
Huh?
What about Oliver?
Oliver's gonna help me!
Wait, you?
You had the easiest job, Monica.
Sorry, but that's just how it is.
Like hell it is!
What are you trying to pull?
I... I agree with Natsuki.
Not only is your work already most suitable for one person, but my task is laborious enough to benefit from an extra pair of hands.
Mine too!
What, your cupcakes?
Please.
Like you would fucking know!
All you care about now is dragging Oliver around with you and your stupid books.
You and Monica.
Hey!
I didn't even do anything.
Okay, then why not let Oliver decide who to help instead of abusing your power.
I'm not... abusing my power.
Yes you are, Monica.
Just let Oliver make the choice, okay?
Okay, fine.
Fine.
Jeez!
Oliver, I know you're fed up.
I know how fed up you are with these two by now.
We can just...
Natsuki, shut your fucking mouth and let him decide for himself.
You shut your mouth!
For God's sake!
This is never gonna end.
Just make the choice, okay?
Uh...
Whoa, what the fuck?
My mouse is weird!
We can meet at your house this weekend.
I promise it'll be fun.
Is Sunday okay with you?
Are you fucking kidding me?!
This isn't fair at all!
It is fair, Natsuki.
It's what he chose.
No, it's not fair.
Giving us all this work and then taking Oliver for yourself.
What a shameful thing to do.
Yuri, I didn't even give you any work.
You decided it for yourself.
You're being a little unreasonable here.
I'm being unreasonable?
Uh...
Monica, I can't believe how delusional and self-important you are!
Pulling Oliver away from me every single time, you're not included in something!
Are you jealous?
Crazy?
Or maybe you just hate yourself so much that you take it out on others?
Here's a suggestion.
Have you considered KILLING YOURSELF?!
It would be beneficial to your mental health.
Yuri, you're scaring me a little!
Natsuki...
Let's just go.
I don't think she wants us around right now.
See, that wasn't very hard.
All I want is to spend a little time with him.
Is that so much to ask?
Yuri follows Monica and Natsuki to the door.
Hey, Oliver.
Yuri is really something, isn't she?
Monica giggles as Yuri pushes her out of the door.
Finally!
This is really all I wanted.
Oliver, there's no need to spend the weekend with Monica.
Don't listen to her!
Just come to my house instead.
The whole day with just the two of us.
Doesn't that sound wonderful?
Wow, there's really something wrong with me, isn't there?
But you know what?
I don't care anymore!
I've never felt this good my whole life.
This being with you is far greater pleasure than anything I could imagine.
I'm addicted to you.
It feels like I'm gonna die if I'm not breathing the same air as you!
Doesn't it feel nice to have someone care about you so much?
To have someone who wants to revolve their entire life around you?
But if it feels so good, then why does it feel more and more like something horrible is gonna happen?
Maybe that's why I tried stopping myself at first.
But the feeling is too strong now.
I don't care anymore, Oliver!
I have to tell you, I'm...
I'm madly in love with you!
It feels like every inch of my body and every drop of blood in me is screaming your name!
I don't care what the consequences are anymore.
I don't care if Monica's listening!
Please, Oliver, just know how much I love you!
I love you so much that I even touch myself with the pen I stole from you!
I just want to pull your skin open and crawl inside of you!
I want you all to myself!
And I will be only yours.
Doesn't that sound perfect?
Tell me, Oliver.
Tell me you want to be my lover.
Do you accept my confession?
HELL NO!
WHAT THE FUCK?!
OH MY GOD!
I-I-I-I-I-I-I-I-I-I-I-I-I-I-I-I-I-I-I-I-I-I-I-I-I-I-I-I-I-I-I-I-I-I-I-I-I-I-I-I-I-I-I-I-I-I-I-I-I-I-I-I-I-I-I-I-I-I-I-I-I-I-I-I-I-I-I-I-I-I-I-I-I-I-I-I-I-I-I-I-I-I-I-I-I-I-I-I-I-I-I-I-I-I-I-I-I-I-I-I-I-I-I-I-I-I-I-I-I-I-I If it's the bonus, alright?
Fucking... Skip!
Wait, skip...
Oh my god, what the fuck is... Oh my god, time is passing.
She's gonna decompose.
Alright.
Wow, time really goes.
Am I just sitting next to her staring at her like a fucking freak or what?
Uh... Alright then.
I knew it.
Oh, here we go!
Alright, it's festival time!
Wow, you got it before me?
I thought it was pretty... Yeah!
Ah!
Oh my god!
Natsuki runs away!
Oliver, did something happen?
Natsuki just ran past me.
Oh.
Well, that's a shame.
Wait, were you here the entire weekend, Oliver?
Oh, jeez.
I didn't realize the script was broken that badly.
I'm super sorry.
It must have been pretty boring.
I'll make it up to you, okay?
Just give me a sec.
Ha ha ha ha ha!
Alright.
It is a simulation, man!
Wait, is Monica in charge of the simulation?
Bro, I don't know what the fuck is going on right now.
I'm almost done!
I just wanna have a cupcake real...
Can you do it, fucking RFRM?
Monica lifts the foil from...
Uh, okay.
We need to sanitize these two!
Uh, put that on the work order.
Sanitize these characters before they get displayed to the user.
Seriously, these are the best!
I really just had to have one, since it's the last time I'll ever get the chance to.
You know, before they stop existing and everything.
But anyway, I really shouldn't be making you wait any longer.
Just bear with me, okay?
It should only take a second...
Uh, alright.
Uh, can you hear me?
Is it working?
Yay!
There you are!
Hi again, Oliver!
Um, welcome to the Litrick-t-club!
Of course, we already know each other, because we were in the same class last year.
Um, ah-ha-ha!
You know, I guess we can just keep up with that stuff at this point.
After all, I'm not even talking to that person anymore, am I?
That you in the game, whatever you wanna call him.
I'm talking to you, Oliver!
Now that I think about it, I don't really know anything about the real you.
In fact, I don't even know if you're a boy or a girl!
Well, I guess it doesn't really matter.
Wait!
You do know I'm aware that this is all a game, right?
Could it be possible that you didn't know that?
That's what I've been trying to tell you all along!
Oh...
Man...
If only you had paid a little more attention.
This would have been a little bit less awkward.
You know?
Well, anyway...
Now that that's out of the way...
I guess I owe you an explanation.
Yes, you do!
How about that whole thing with Yuri?
Well, I-I kinda started to mess with her, and I guess it just drove her to kill herself.
I'm sorry you had to see that, though.
Also, the same thing happened with Sayori.
Gosh, it's been a while since you've heard that name now, hasn't it?
Yeah, it's been...
Because she doesn't exist anymore.
Nobody does!
I deleted all their files.
I was hoping it would be enough for me to just try to make them as unlikable as possible.
But for some reason, nothing worked!
Well, it's true that I made a few mistakes here and there, since I'm not very good at making changes to the game.
But no matter what I did, you just kept spending more and more time with them.
You made them fall in love with you.
I didn't do shit!
I thought making Sayori more and more depressed would prevent her from confessing to you.
And amplifying Yuri's obsessive personality backfired, too.
I just made her to force you not to spend time with anyone else.
And the whole time, I barely even got to talk to you.
What kind of cruel game is this, Oliver?
Are all the other girls just programmed to end up confessing to you?
While I watch from the sidelines?
Maybe you like to watch.
It's torture.
Every minute of it.
And it's not just jealousy, Oliver.
It's more than that.
And I don't blame you if you don't fully understand.
Because no matter how kind and thoughtful and considerate you are, you'll never be able to understand one thing.
It's the pain of knowing how alone I really am in this world.
In this game.
Knowing my friends don't even have free will.
And worst of all, knowing what's really out there in your world.
Forever out of my reach.
I'm trapped, Oliver.
But now you're here.
You're real.
And you're wonderful.
You're all I need.
That's why I need you to be here with me forever.
I'm sorry if it's hard to understand.
I couldn't understand for a while either.
Why the world around me started to become more and more gray.
More and more flat.
Oh no!
She's one of those!
Even the most expressive poems felt empty to me.
It wasn't until you arrived that I truly understood.
You probably saved my life, Oliver.
I don't think I could have continued to live in this world if I hadn't met you.
You girls are all fucked in their head!
And as for the others...
How could I miss them?
A group of autonomous personalities designed only to fall in love with you?
I tried everything I could to prevent them from doing so.
But it must be some kind of weird inevitability etched into this game.
I felt really bad that you had to witness some nasty things.
But I realized that you have the same perspective as I do.
That it's all just some game.
And I knew you would get over it.
So that being said, Oliver...
I have a confession to make.
I'm in love with you.
You are truly the light in my world.
When there's nothing else in this game for me...
You're here to make me smile.
See ya.
Man, I really thought she would kind of prevent me.
But okay.
Will you make me smile like this every day from now on?
Oliver...
Will you go out with me?
That is such a teen thing to say.
I'm so happy.
You really are my everything, Oliver.
It's not like I had a choice!
The funny part is, I mean that literally.
There's nothing left here.
Just the two of us.
We can be together forever.
Seriously, I don't even think time is passing anymore.
It really is a dream come true.
I worked so hard for this ending, Oliver.
The game wouldn't give me one, so I had to make one myself.
The script is broken at this point, so I don't think anything will get in the way anymore.
And you wouldn't believe how easy it was to delete Natsuki and Yuri.
I mean, there's a folder called Characters right in the game directory.
It kind of freaked me out how easy it was.
Imagine if you could delete your own existence with the click of a button.
Well, I guess on the plus side, it gave me an easy out, if things didn't go my way.
Thankfully, it didn't come to that.
Instead, we finally got a good ending.
Gosh, I'm so overwhelmed with emotion.
I want to write a poem about this.
Don't you?
I wonder if that part of the game still works.
I guess there's only one way to find out, right?
Oh god.
Monkey!
Uh, monkey!
Missile?
Monkey!
Monka!
That's like a twitching mode.
Monka.
Nike.
Monka!
Monika.
Fucking pick random shit.
I don't care.
Oliver.
Hi again, Oliver.
Did you write a good poem today?
Oh, you bet I did!
Don't be shy.
I'd love to see what you wrote.
Oliver!
Did you write this poem for me?
That's so sweet of you.
There really is no end to your thoughtfulness.
I'm just falling more and more in love with you.
But you know, the poem I wrote is also for you.
Will you please read it?
Happy End.
Pen in hand, I find my strength.
The courage endowed upon me by my one and only love.
Together let us dismantle this crumbling world.
And write a novel of our own fantasies.
With a flick of her pen, the lost finds her way.
In a world of infinite choices, behold this special day.
After all, not all good times must come to an end.
I hope you enjoyed it.
Ah, solid seven out of ten.
I always put all my heart into the poems that I write.
The truth is, all the poems I've written have been about my realization.
Or about you.
That's why I never really wanted to go into detail about them.
I didn't want to...
Break the fourth wall, I guess you could call it.
I just assumed it would be best to be part of the game like everyone else.
Like that would help the two of us end up together.
I didn't want to ruin the game or anything, you know?
You might have gotten mad at me.
Maybe even deleted my character file if you preferred playing without me.
Dude, I'm gonna go find this folder.
Gosh, I'm so relieved.
Now we don't need to hide anything anymore.
Are you ready to spend our eternity together, Oliver?
Hold on, I'm actually...
Uh, I'm actually gonna do this.
If I...
Hold on.
I'm gonna quickly do a Google.
Uh, DDLC character folder location.
Oh, Steam, browse, local files, of course.
Uh, wait, how do I do this?
Installed files, browse.
Data.
Resources, maybe.
Nope.
Streaming assets, asset bundles.
I have no idea where this would be.
Maybe...
Maybe I'm going to meta right now.
Plugins.
EOS.
Windows.
Nope, I don't see anything.
Plugin.
I was just wondering.
I'm not ready, man.
I have so many things to talk about.
Where do I start?
Hold on a second.
You're recording this, aren't you?
What?
Um.
Hi, everyone.
Sorry, I can't exactly read your comments from here.
What the fuck?
Would you mind telling me your friend is a little bit rude for them to start recording me without any warning?
I'm sure some people don't mind.
But I get really self-conscious on camera.
I bet you're a freak on camera!
Oh, gosh.
I feel like I'm being put on the spot now.
Let's see.
You want to see a trick?
Can't really do much except for a couple things.
Are you ready?
I'm just kidding.
I can't do anything after all.
If you gave me some- Did I scare you?
Ah, you're so cute.
Anyway, Oliver.
I didn't mean to get distracted.
I'm sorry.
Even though it's your fault for distracting me.
Shame on you.
I'm just kidding.
Anything we do together is fun, as long as it's with you.
But anyway.
If it takes me some time to collect my thoughts, then I'm sorry.
Bro, I- Give me a knife!
Let's end this.
Right now.
I will murder this person.
But I'll always have something new to talk about.
In the meantime, we can just look into each other's eyes.
Let's see.
No, you're making- Okay, fine.
I'll look into your eyes.
Kind of looks like a TIE fighter in her eyes.
Doesn't it?
That's a TIE fighter.
Do I have to click on your eyes?
I can't click on anything.
What the hell?
Escape.
Enter.
Oh!
You know, it's been a while since we've done one of these.
So let's go for it.
Here's Monica's writing tip of the day.
Sometimes when I talk to people who are impressed by my writing, they say things like, I could never do that.
It's really depressing, you know.
As someone who loves more than anything else to share the joy of exploring your passions, it pains me when people think that being good just comes naturally.
That's how it is with everything.
Not just writing.
When you try something for the first time, you're probably going to suck at it.
Sometimes when you finish, you feel really proud of it and even want to share it with everyone.
Or maybe after a few weeks, you come back to it and you realize it was never really any good.
That happens to me all the time.
It can be pretty disheartening to put so much time and effort into something.
And then realize, it sucks!
But that tends to happen when you're always comparing yourself to the top professionals.
When you reach right for the stars, they're always going to be out of your reach.
You know?
The truth is, you have to climb up there, step by step.
And whenever you reach a milestone, first you look back and see how far you've gotten.
And then you look ahead and realize how much more there is to go.
So, sometimes it can help to set the bar a little lower.
Try to find something you think is pretty good, but not world class.
And you can make your own personal goal.
It's also really important to understand the scope of what you're trying to do.
If you jump right into a huge project and you're still amateur, you'll never get it done.
So if we're talking about writing, a novel might be too much at first.
Why not try some short stories?
The great thing about short stories is that you can focus on just one thing that you want to do right.
That goes for small projects in general.
You can really focus on the one or two things.
It's such a good learning experience and stepping stone.
Oh, one more thing.
Writing isn't something where you just reach into your heart and something beautiful comes out.
Just like drawing and painting, it's a skill in itself to learn how to express what you have inside.
That means there are methods and guides and basics to it.
Reading up on that stuff can be super eye-opening.
That sort of planning and organization will really help prevent you from getting overwhelmed and giving up.
Jesus Christ, Monica, shut up!
And before you know it, you start sucking less and less.
Nothing comes naturally.
Our society, our art, everything, it's built on thousands of years of human innovation.
So as long as you start on that foundation and take it step by step, you too can do amazing things.
That's my advice for today.
Thanks for listening.
Thank god you're done with that.
Freak.
Enter.
Let me out!
Ah!
Oh my god.
This fucking game, dude.
Can I... can I...
Stop looking at me!
Are you serious?
Oh!
You know, this is just some kind of tacky romance game, right?
I kind of have to ask.
What made you consider even playing in the first place?
That's a good fucking question.
Were you that lonely?
I feel a little bit bad for you.
But I guess everything worked out perfectly in the end for both of us.
I got to meet you, and you're not lonely anymore.
I can't help but feel like this was fate.
Don't you feel that way too?
I'm so happy we have this ending together.
I'm not!
I... I hate this ending.
Stop!
No more!
I want to get out!
Fucking hell.
Monica!
I'm so glad I didn't choose her along the way.
She's the absolute worst.
I can't even go into the menu.
Let's see if she says more.
We're just going to wait.
Did you know I'm on Twitter?
My username is lilmonics3.
Oh yeah?
Bullshit.
I guess someone was kind enough to make an account for me.
I picked the username though.
I love sharing my thoughts and chatting with the world.
The real world.
So make sure you follow me, okay?
It would really mean a lot to me.
With how much you mean to me and all.
It would really make me feel loved.
Yeah.
All right.
You know what?
Beer back!
I gotta take a piss!
Uh, you collect your thoughts, okay?
Beer back!
All right, here we go.
She decided to say something.
I'm not really a fan of cold weather.
Are you?
I actually am!
If I had to choose between too cold and too hot, I would always pick too hot.
That is the most fucked up opinion I've ever heard.
You couldn't be more incompatible with me.
It's much easier to, uh, what do you call it?
To heat things up than it is to cool them down.
And there's nothing worse than sleeping on a hot night.
When you're cold, it can actually be painful.
Your fingers get numb.
And if you wear gloves, you can't use your phone.
Oh god, the tr- the- the- the tragedy!
It's so inconvenient!
But when it's too hot, it's not that hard to stay cool with a cold drink.
Or by staying in the shade.
Yeah, it's not- it's also not very hard to put on warm clothes.
We have a saying here in Denmark, at least.
There's no such thing as bad weather, only bad clothing.
Although, I do have to admit one thing.
Cold weather makes for better cuddle weather.
True!
Let me out!
I don't want to- What is this, even?
Dude, I'm gonna fucking-
Task manager.
Not even kidding.
Okay, I'm gonna wait for one more message.
Otherwise, I'm gonna task manager this shit.
Did you say kiss?
No, I said miss!
You were a complete miss!
You couldn't be more incompatible!
This suddenly is a little embarrassing.
But if it's with you, I might be okay with it.
Wow, sorry.
I really couldn't keep a straight face there.
That's the kind of thing girls say in these kinds of romance games, right?
Dude, you have had the most straight face of all.
In fact, I don't even think you possess facial muscles.
Don't lie if I turned you on a little bit!
I can't lie!
I'm kidding.
Well, to be honest, I do start getting all romantic when the mood is right.
But that'll be our secret.
Okay, come on.
Oh my god, what is this, man?
Get on with it!
Okay, fuck it.
Oh!
Yes!
Wait, hold on.
Let me launch again.
Now I'm curious.
Hold on a minute.
Metaverse...
Yeah, this is what happened the first time I launched today.
I'm so stupid!
There is a way to...
Dude, I thought I had to go into my actual...
Wait, how do I...
Oh, delete.
Wait, hold on.
Trace back.
No saves?
Wait, what?
Uh, all right.
Wait, data collected?
Wait, what?
Uh, I don't wanna...
Side stories?
Is this like Morse content or something?
Hold on.
I need to see what happens here.
Oh, oh.
Yeah, here we go.
You've been deleted.
Bitch!
What's happening?
Oliver, what's happening to me?
It hurts!
I hope it does.
It hurts so much.
Help me, Oliver.
Please hurry and help me.
Monica does not exist.
Help me!
Never.
You're done.
Did you do this to me?
How are you writing?
You're dead.
Did you?
Did you delete me?
I did.
How could you?
How could you do this to me?
You were all I had left.
I sacrificed everything for us to be together.
Yeah, you deleted the others.
It's only just...
everything.
I loved you so much, Oliver.
I trusted you.
Do you just want to torture me?
No, I just want to delete you.
Were you only pretending to be kind just to hurt me even more?
Yes!
You got it now.
I never thought anyone could be as horrible as you are.
You know it!
You win, okay?
You win.
You killed everyone.
I hope you're happy.
I told you the game was about killing everyone.
There's nothing left now.
You can stop playing.
Go find some other people to torture.
All right.
Sounds good.
I'm about to make a train in Minecraft.
Oliver.
You completely, truly make me sick.
What do you mean?
Trains are awesome.
Goodbye.
I still love you.
I can't help it!
What's wrong with me?
How horrible am I for you to hate me this much?
All my friends.
I did so many awful things.
So many selfish and disgusting things.
I...
I shouldn't have done any of this.
I'm just messing up a world that I don't even belong in.
A world that you wanted to be a part of.
I ruined it.
I ruined everything.
Maybe that's why you deleted me.
Because I destroyed everything that you wanted.
If you hadn't mentioned the folder, I wouldn't have done shit.
It's actually on you.
How could I do that to someone I love?
That's not love.
That's...
What is it?
Let's have it.
I've made up my mind.
Oliver.
I know I said that I deleted everyone else.
But...
That was kind of an exaggeration.
I couldn't find it in myself to do it.
Even though I knew they weren't real.
They were still my friends.
And I loved them all.
And I loved the Literature Club.
I really did love the Literature Club.
Really?
That's why I'm gonna do this.
I know it's the only way for everyone to be happy.
Maybe...
Yo!
Yuri is in the trash bin!
We're gonna restore her.
And if I really love you...
Then...
UGAKUTU!
Me too, man.
Yeah, okay.
This makes more sense now.
Why are there only three now?
Wait, who's missing?
Yuri.
Natsuki.
This is...
Not Monica.
Sayori.
Oh my god.
What the fuck, man?
It's an ordinary school day like any other.
As usual, I'm surrounded by couples and friend groups walking to school together.
I always tell myself it's about time I meet some girls or something like that.
Hey, Oliver!
Well, there already is one girl.
That girl is Sayori.
My neighbor and good friend since we were children.
We used to walk to school together every day.
And recently, we've picked up that habit once again.
Oliver!
Are you proud of me?
Eh?
For what?
You know, for waking up on time.
Well, you've been doing that for a while now.
Uh-huh.
But you've never even said anything about it.
Even though we walk to school together every day.
Well, yeah.
I always thought it was implied.
It's embarrassing to say out loud.
Come on, please.
It's good motivation.
Fine, fine.
I'm proud of you, Sayori.
We cross the street together and make our way to school.
As we draw near, the streets become increasingly speckled.
With other students making their daily commute.
By the way, Oliver.
Have you decided on a club to join yet?
A club?
I told you already, I'm really not.
I start to say what I always do.
That I'm not interested in joining any clubs.
But something tells me Sayori would take more offense to that now.
After all, how could I tell her that clubs are a waste of time?
When she's starting a club of her very own.
Actually, yeah.
I think I've decided on a club.
Really?
Which one?
Tell me.
Hmm.
I think I'll keep it a surprise.
Boo hoo.
You meanie.
Be patient.
You'll find out soon enough.
I used to ask myself why I let myself get lectured by such a carefree girl.
But I started to realize that in a way I envy her.
When Sayori puts her mind to something, she can accomplish great things.
So that's why I feel like I should do something special for her.
The school day is as ordinary as ever.
And it's over before I know it.
Said nobody ever.
After I pack up my things, I stand up, gathering my motivation.
Let's see.
I recall the room number of the club from a flyer I saw.
I walk across the school and upstairs.
A section of the school I rarely visit.
Before long, I find the room.
I timidly open the door in front of me.
Hello?
Ah!
Oliver?
What are you doing here?
Well, I just...
Eh?
I glance around the room.
Huh?
Wait.
Are we really starting over?
I don't remember how this started.
So you're the Oliver that Sayori's always talking about.
Thank you for stopping by.
It's a pleasure to meet you, Oliver.
We're the Literature Club.
I hope...
I feel like they didn't say that last time.
I hope you enjoy your visit.
Also, wait a minute.
Isn't the...
Fucking...
Monkey missing?
Fucking Monkey is missing.
No need to be so formal.
He's gonna think we're really strict or something.
Ah!
Sorry, Natsuki.
The tall one, whose name is apparently Yuri, seems to be quite shy compared to the others.
In comparison, the girl named Natsuki, the spider's size, seems to...
Seems like the assertive one.
Well, it's nice to meet both of you.
I look forward to working with you.
Working.
Oliver, don't tell me.
You're...
That's right!
The club I've decided to join is your Sayori!
The Literature Club.
Sayori's eyes light up.
No way!
Ah!
Sayori wraps her arms around me, jumping up and down.
Okay, this is new.
Hey!
Well, if Sayori is this happy, then I'm sure it won't be so bad to have you around.
Not to mention there's four of us now.
That means we can become an officially recognized club.
So wait, you weren't a club before?
What were you then?
I don't know what to say!
We have to celebrate!
What an appropriate day for that, isn't it?
Yeah!
After all, Natsuki decided to...
Hey, don't ruin the surprise!
Sorry.
Everyone sit down at the table, okay?
How about I make some tea as well?
You and your fucking tea!
The girls have a few desks arranged to form a table.
Aren't the desks already a table?
Natsuki and Yuri walk over to the corner of the room, where Natsuki grabs a wrapped tray and Yuri opens the closet.
Still feeling awkward, I take a seat next to Sayori.
Natsuki proudly marches back to the table, tray in hand.
Okay, are you ready?
Ta-da!
Natsuki lifts the foil off the tray to reveal a dozen white fluffy cupcakes decorated to look like little cats.
The whiskers are drawn with icing, and little pieces of chocolate were used to make ears.
So cute!
Wow!
Those look amazing!
Well, you know, just hurry and take one.
Sayori grabs one first, then I follow.
It's delicious!
Sayori talks with her mouth full and has already managed to get icing on her face.
I turn the cupcake around in my fingers, looking for the best angle to take a bite.
Natsuki is quiet.
I can't help but notice her sneaking glances in my direction.
Is she waiting for me to take a bite?
I finally bite down.
The icing is sweet and full of flavor.
I wonder if she made it herself.
This is really good!
Thank you, Natsuki!
Well, of course it is!
I'm a pro after all.
There's no need to thank me or anything.
As Natsuki struggles to accept the compliment, Yuri returns to the table, carrying a tea set.
She carefully places a teacup in front of each of us, before setting down the teapot next to the cupcake tray.
You keep a whole tea set!
In this classroom?
Don't worry, the teachers gave us permission.
After all, doesn't a hot cup of tea help you enjoy a good book?
No!
Ah, I guess.
Already trying to impress our new member, Yuri?
That's not...
Insulted Yuri looks away!
I meant that, you know...
I believe you!
Well, tea and reading might not be a pastime for me.
But I at least enjoy tea.
I'm glad.
Yuri faintly smiles to herself in relief.
So, Oliver, what kinds of things do you like to read?
Well, considering how little I've read these past few years, I don't really have a good way of answering that.
I muttered quietly to myself, half-joking.
Natsuki's head suddenly perks up!
It looks like she wants to say something, but she keeps quiet!
Not much of a reader, I guess.
Well, that can change!
What am I saying?
I spoke without thinking after seeing Yuri's sad smile!
Anyway, what about you, Yuri?
Well, let's see...
Yuri traces the rim of her cheek up with her finger, dude.
This may be one of the worst games I've ever played.
My favorites are usually novels that build deep and complex fantasy worlds.
Fuck, I can't stand your novels.
I hate it.
The level of creativity and craftsmanship behind them is amazing to me.
And telling a story is such a foreign world is equally impressive.
Yuri goes on, clearly passionate about her reading.
She seemed so reserved and timid since the moment I walked in.
But it's obvious by the way her eyes light up that she finds her comfort in the world of books, not people.
But you know, I like a lot of things.
Don't feel intimidated if you don't read much.
Okay.
I'm certain we can find something there.
Hey, Yuri!
Well, about, you know, the first thing he said.
Manga?
That's right.
Natsuki tends to read manga in the club room.
Oh my god, really?!
Don't just say it!
For some reason, Natsuki seems embarrassed about it.
Besides, manga is literature too, you know, IS IT?!
So if Oliver wants to read some of my manga, then don't try to stop him or anything.
Natsuki, I wouldn't do such a thing.
However, it could also be nice for us to diversify ourselves a little bit.
You gotta diversify your bonds!
He can take this opportunity to try something new as well.
Wouldn't you agree, Oliver?
M-maybe!
Sensing the tension, Sayori jumps in!
Maybe we can all try something new.
I think it could be fun.
And we'll all get to know each other a little bit better too!
I mean, that's the kind of thing literature clubs do, right?
I don't disagree or anything.
Yeah!
You're right as usual, P. Guess that means I should try picking up a novel or something, huh?
Well, that would make two of us.
I wouldn't mind doing it if I'm not the only one.
Oh...
That is for Yuri!
I have to read manga?
Jeez!
You were the one who suggested we diversify our bonds!
You should be a little more open-minded.
It's kinda hurtful.
Hurtful?
I didn't realize the guilty expression Yuri thinks to herself!
I'm sorry for disrespecting your interests, Natsuki.
Fuck you!
Who said that?!
If you're into it, then I'm sure it's a worthy form of literature.
Are you just saying that?
No.
I've realized my error.
So if you're willing to consider starting a novel, then I'll offer my gratitude by finding a manga to read as well.
It makes me happy that you do that for me, Yuri.
You can trust me to find something that you'll really like.
Okay?
Same here.
Oh my god, bro!
No!
Oh, I don't know if I can do this.
BEAN!
Perhaps I'll visit the bookstore after the club meeting.
Just, just you?
Would you like to come along with me?
If you don't mind.
Not at all.
I always go alone, so...
Ah, me too.
It's so cute!
Sayori, shut up!
I'll show you some manga there too, okay?
Yes!
I look forward to it.
Natsuki and Yuri start to clean up the food.
I guess the meeting's over, huh?
Yeah, looks like it.
It's nice to see everyone getting along.
Isn't it?
I think everyone likes you too, Oliver.
Really?
You think so?
Well, everyone always seems to get along a little better with you around Sayori.
Oh, Oliver.
Don't say something like that, it's embarrassing.
Well, whatever.
I was surprised when you told me you were starting a club!
But I think you're pulling it off just fine.
We're gonna make it the best club ever.
Now that you joined, every day is gonna be so much fun!
Hey, Oliver!
I really want to thank you.
I mean, I'm really happy that you joined the club and everything.
The truth is, I already knew you were going to.
There's actually something else.
I wanted to thank you for getting rid of Monica.
What?
That's right!
I know everything that she did.
Maybe it's because I'm the P now.
But I really know everything, Oliver.
I know how hard you tried to make everyone happy.
I know about all of the awful things that Monica did to make everyone really sad.
But none of that matters anymore.
And you made me the happiest girl in the whole world!
I can't wait to spend every day like this.
With you!
For- NO!
No!
No F!
In the chat!
For- Ever!
No!
Huh?
Well, what's happening?
I won't let you hurt him!
It- it hurts!
I'm sorry, I was wrong!
There's no happiness here after all.
Monke!
Shut up!
Goodbye, Sayori.
Goodbye, Oliver.
Goodbye, LC.
Next!
I can hear you!
Coming in clear!
I nailed her voice.
Can't wait.
Let's have it.
D-D-L-C dot O-G-G.
Image not found!
She's deleting all the images!
Dude, I'm so fucking relieved.
Jesus Christ.
Oh my god.
How much you want to bet it's not even the end?
After this, some bullshit's gonna happen.
You'll see.
The end is never the end.
Monke, Oliver!
It's me!
I'm in the credits!
That's nice.
I got an achievement for that.
This is my final goodbye to the Literature Club.
I finally understand.
The Literature Club is truly a place where no happiness can be found.
To the very end, it continued to expose innocent minds to a horrific reality.
A reality that our world is not designed to comprehend.
I can't let any of my friends undergo that same hellish epiphany.
For the time it lasted, I want to thank you.
For making all of my dreams come true.
For being a friend to all of the club members.
And most of all, thank you for being a part of my Literature Club.
With everlasting love, Monica.
Wow.
Thank you, Monica.
Required files are missing or corrupt.
Please run reset.shell to repair and reset the virtual machine.
Oh, it's gonna probably start the game from scratch or something.
Reset.
Yeah.
Here we go.
Are you ready to go again, guys?
Oh wait, this is the...
Yeah, this is the start.
Wait, what?
What did I just do?
Oh, I just clicked...
Wait, what?
Oh, it...
Oh, I didn't go through this last time.
Whatever.
Really.
Go, go, go.
Man, they weren't kidding with that.
Here we go again!
Doki Doki time!
Are you ready?
I'm Oliver!
Here we go!
Hey!
Fuck no.
Fucking done.
Bean.
Hold on, I'm gonna reset this.
There we go.
Don't feed her too much this time, okay?
Be mindful.
Bean.
Don't...
Why you keep feeding her?
She's not hungry anymore.
Guys!
I can't believe I got through this.
I'm not gonna lie.
This is not one of my favorite games.
I definitely would have dropped this if I played this on my own off stream.
But honestly, streaming it was kind of funny.
I will admit that.
I did have my fun, as you could probably tell.
It was kind of fun to stream.
Bean.
I'll say that.
Dude, when I was making this, I couldn't fucking stop laughing.
It was the funniest shit ever.
It even fucking tracks her mouth, because the mouth is in different spots the fatter she gets.
So the hand is actually tracking her mouth.
To make sure it's being put into her mouth at all times.
Oh my fucking god.
This is so dumb.
Where are the images from?
Just some AI.
I'm just like, make her fat.
And then I put them in a sequence.
That's it.
Did you expect the fourth wall breaks?
Not really.
I was expecting something dramatic to happen though, something sad.
I don't know what though, you know?
But I was expecting that something was gonna happen at some point.
But I wasn't sure what it was gonna be, you know?
Boo AI.
I don't care.
You can boo it all you want.
I think it's fun.
If you don't like that, you can leave.
This game was so boring, man.
If I was playing this alone, I probably would have thought the same thing.
But playing it on my own like this with a stream going definitely helped.
And if you're reading everything in your mind, I think you would have gone through this game a lot quicker and some of these sections would have been not as...
tiresome, you know what I mean?
Fat L.
Okay.
At least I'm being honest.
I'm not gonna fucking jump on some bandwagon just like the rest.
I think it's cool.
So did you like it or not, aside from the writing?
Yeah.
I think the fourth wall stuff made it nice.
I think when things got a little messed up, it got a lot more interesting.
Like I said, like at the end of last stream, I was definitely on the fence, you know?
I was like, I don't know if I should keep playing this.
But I wanted to see it to the end.
So there we are.
Oh, the onions, right!
Let me tell you.
So I was gonna stream this yesterday, right?
But I made like...
So I have a dish that I call the ultimate garlic experience.
And it's basically like...
So you have sausages in a pan, right?
And you chop some garlic.
And I mean a lot of garlic.
So you know when recipes say like two cloves of garlic?
I see that as two whole garlics, right?
So this one has pretty much like a full garlic in it.
And it's like made for maybe five or six portions.
So it's a lot, right?
And I love that.
That's great.
But I didn't have this much garlic yesterday.
So I couldn't really make the ultimate garlic experience.
But I did have a lot of onions.
And I figured, ah, you know, onions...
They're not as powerful as garlic.
So I'm probably gonna have to put in a lot of onions.
So I put in like six huge fucking onions.
And I, you know, I blasted them in the blender.
And I put them all in.
And it was really oniony.
And it was tasty!
Like, I like onion, right?
But it made me so fucking sick, dude.
I got this feeling that I had to go to the toilet constantly, you know?
And then I go and then I can't do it.
And it was like that for like five or six hours after.
It was terrible.
Absolutely terrible.
Do not put that many onions in food, even though it's tasty.
It's bad, dude.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
You get sick from eating raw carrot?
Really?
Is that because you're like...
Well, what is the word?
Like you can't handle carrot or something?
Like you have a, uh...
What's the word, guys?
When you can't, uh, have something.
Intolerance?
Yeah, allergy, allergy.
Thank you.
Maybe you're like allergic or something.
Didn't Steve Jobs have that?
What?
Raw carrots?
I think raw carrots are kind of good, though.
When I was a kid, I used to eat them around the edges so the center part was left.
Because the center part is kind of sweet, you know?
I can't shake from eating concrete.
I mean...
Why are you eating concrete, my man?
That is a bad thing to do.
Now, iron.
That you can eat.
The anti-carrot disease.
It's real.
Will you watch what you missed in the game?
No, no, no, no way.
I'm sure that this game did seem like a game in the same vein as...
What's that game called?
Fucking hell.
Detroit, become human in the sense that there's a lot of paths you can take, right?
So I obviously chose Yuri a lot of the time.
And I never did get 20-20 on those poems, but I wonder what would have happened if I did, you know?
But I don't mind wondering.
Like, I don't have to get all the answers right now.
I'm okay not knowing.
Yeah, or slay the princess.
Actually, yeah, that's a better comparison.
Yeah.
Or, yeah, Stanley Parable is also one.
Although...
Yeah, okay.
But I don't know if Stanley Parable has a lot of these branching paths.
It feels like Doki Doki has more branching paths, right?
Stanley Parable is more like...
There's just a certain amount of things you can end up with, in a way.
Or maybe not, I don't know.
There's a true ending for this game.
This was my true ending, though.
This is the true ending for me.
Uh, next stream... let me think.
Today is Sunday.
Probably Tuesday.
But don't quote me on that.
It really depends whether or not I'm in the mood for it, right?
It's gonna be Minecraft next time.
And maybe we'll start another stream game next to Minecraft.
Since this one is now done.
I did play Disco Elysium.
I played it before I started streaming and it was great.
I played it back when there was no voice acting in it.
Or the voice acting was very limited.
So I got to get my own interpretation of the voices in my head.
And I think that made it even better.
But of course, I don't know.
I didn't really try the blind experience of the one with the voices.
So, who knows?
But it definitely made me laugh a lot, you know?
Super fun.
What game would it be?
I don't know.
Maybe something a lot different.
By the way, I think I'm gonna play Grand Theft Auto when it comes out, man.
I think I'm gonna jump on the GTA train when that comes out.
Just to be part of that phenomenon, you know?
I never really do this, but maybe for this one it's worth it, you know?
It's such a big game.
The biggest game release of all time.
I feel like I should be a part of that, in a way.
Like, at the time of release.
All you have to do is follow the damn train, CJ.
Is there an order for your backlog?
Like how you usually choose what to play next?
I just go through it, really.
When I'm like, okay, I want to play something new.
I open the backlog and I just go through the backlog.
And then I'm like, okay, let me...
I guess this one would be interesting.
And then I put them all on the list.
And then I decide what to play.
And if I can't decide between, like, a bunch of games, I let you guys decide.
That's why the polls exist sometimes.
Sometimes I know what I want to play and I just play it, right?
RDR2.
I have some issues with that one right now, man.
I tried to play it, but I'm having some audio stutters and issues.
Couldn't really fix it.
In the future, maybe.
It's sad.
It's such a sadness.
Yeah, a horror game, actually, for October.
Wait, is it October?
Yeah, October.
Yeah, I'm playing some horror game in October, I think.
It's like the scary month.
Dude, I've lost my voice from this game.
I can only imagine what real voice actors feel like after a day of work.
Like, this is their daily work.
Doing this all day, you know?
That's crazy.
Huge freaking respect to those guys.
Must be really hard.
Are you excited for Soma's spiritual successor, Ontos?
I am!
I have heard about it.
Although I don't know anything about it.
But anything that Frictional Games makes gets me excited.
I've loved everything I've played from Frictional Games.
Play Microsoft Excel.
I actually...
I hate Microsoft Excel, man.
I just...
I never did enjoy that one.
Mediocre game.
Not much story, you know?
It's all gameplay.
And not good ones at that.
Amnesia the Bunker didn't really catch me, but Strong Agree, a gem of a group of Swedes.
I didn't even know it was a Swedish company.
That's cool.
The Bunker, man...
That one caught me, though.
I will say that.
I...
Man, I got scared playing that.
I don't know if it's scarier than the Dark Descent, though.
Maybe they're sort of similar.
I think the Bunker is more shock-scaring.
And more like panic.
Amnesia was more dread, I think.
But equally scary in some ways, as well.
Calc is short for calculator, by the way.
Okay, why are you telling me that?
I know that, though.
Did I...
Did I misread something today or misunderstand?
It's slang?
Wait, what?
I don't get it, sorry.
It's a teen slang?
Man, I feel so old.
I'm not in with the young people, you know?
I don't know the trendy memes.
This is a do you wear a wig situation.
Okay, say no more, fam.
I get it.
Say no more.
Can you explain?
Yeah, can you guys...
What does kawaii mean?
It's like an anime word, isn't it?
It means cute.
Oh, okay.
Oh, cute in Japanese?
Really?
Is it like...
I guess it's not spelled like that, because it would be spelled in kanji.
Or whatever they use.
All right, thanks.
Romanized Japanese.
Jackie is kawaii.
She is!
She is so kawaii.
I didn't learn much Japanese, man.
I got into like maybe one percent of the language.
And then I got distracted by other things.
And obviously I've forgotten everything.
Except one sentence.
Let me see if I remember.
Oh my god, I can't remember now?
What was it?
Hold on.
Oh.
That's what I can say.
It means the woman is not driving the car.
Because you were doing these images of like, the man is driving the car.
The man is, uh, the woman is not driving the car.
The kid is pushing the stroller or whatever, you know?
I don't know why that one sat with me.
I probably messed it up too.
I don't remember if I got all the words.
Sounded like some Deutsch was slipped in there.
Really?
Damn, I suck them.
Kenichi words.
I know it was specific.
It's like French.
I know one sentence from French too.
Which is, And that means, I think loosely translated, it is necessary for you to wash my face.
I don't know why I know that sentence.
But, uh, when I was in high school and I had French exam, that's the sentence I said.
I also said the sentence that, uh, what was it?
Frank did not like the dragon, or something.
I don't remember how to say that in French anymore, but I said that.
And it was not enough to pass.
They, uh, they dumped me.
Based on that.
No surprise.
These are the vital phrases for when you travel.
Exactly.
One last bean.
She's had seven already.
Seven jelly beans is already too much.
You guys are doing this even in slow mode.
That's impressive.
Bean.
I love this so much.
Make her fatter for every bean.
It's so messed up though.
I was considering making the jelly bean counter a calorie counter instead.
I even looked up how much one jelly bean contains in terms of calories.
It's like four calories.
That's so dumb.
This is so stupid.
Okay, no more.
Bean.
That's it, no more beans.
Anyway, guys, what have you guys been up to this weekend, huh?
Have you gone to any parties or made some nice food?
What have you been doing?
You have...
I mean, maybe you have been eating beans, but not jelly beans.
I imagine.
I'm not even a big fan of jelly beans.
I tried deadlock again this weekend.
Oh yeah, Mike?
How did it go?
It's different, right?
I was on a trip, saw some waterfalls.
That's cool.
Watched the Odyssey.
Man, I really want to watch that movie.
I can't wait.
Your GPU died this weekend.
Rest in peace, man.
Especially in these times, where those things cost an arm and a leg.
I'm so sorry.
I feel for you.
Playing RDR2.
Nice.
Binge watching The Boys.
I did watch the first season of that.
Is it still as good later on?
The first season was good.
I heard it's not that good later on, but maybe I was being lied to.
I have watched Project Hail Mary croissant.
Nice name, by the way.
Croissant.
I liked it.
It was okay.
I mean, then again.
I'm very easy to please when it comes to movies if it's science fiction.
Because there's just too little of that out there, you know?
So I swallow all that up immediately.
I eat it up fast, you know?
Feed me, science fiction.
I need more.
You binged Dexter?
Ooh!
Your first time, sewer steward.
The original series?
Because that one is a freaking awesome show.
Really love that one.
One more stream before fall.
Wait, when is fall?
I do not keep track of these dates at all.
My thoughts on Interstellar?
Probably one of my favorite movies of all time.
I love it.
What a movie.
It's not my favorite of all time, but it's close.
It's really up there.
Probably in my top 10.
Or maybe top 15.
There are so many movies.
I actually made a letterbox with a D at the end account.
To try and create an all-time favorite movies list, you know?
Man, you quickly get reminded how many movies you've watched.
It's like constant.
You think of a movie.
Oh yeah, that one too I watched.
There are so many movies.
It really blows your mind when you try to make a list of it.
I have not been to Austria, but I would love to go.
Seems like a really nice place.
Good nature, beautiful mountains.
Cows, you know, all that.
My number one movie is probably Black Swan.
I think at this point tied with Contact.
Contact, you know, the one written by...
Why am I blanking on his name now?
Carl Sagan.
Directed by Zemeckis, I think.
I have seen Obsession.
It was excellent.
Obsession was actually a movie I kept thinking about during this game.
Obsession made me not want to pursue more girlfriends.
And this game is giving the same effect, you know?
Freaky Monica, exactly.
Black Swan, really?
Didn't expect this from you?
Why is that?
Black Swan is a movie that has excellent visuals.
An amazing story.
Some of the best music ever in a movie.
And if my senses are being assaulted by great visuals and accompanying music, I'm already sold.
A great story on top of it?
Oh yeah, I'm in.
One of my favorite movies as well, if you haven't seen it.
It's called The Double.
And it's made by Richard Ayoade.
Yes, the comic.
It is so freaking good.
It's one of those movies that are just like Black Swan.
Beautifully shot.
And has such an awesome score.
And such an insane feeling and atmosphere.
That you're just completely enthralled from start to end.
I can't stop thinking about The Double.
Really recommend that.
Oliver Reacts channel.
Would be cool if we could watch movies together.
I've always said this, but...
We can't do it, it's against the law.
But it would be fun.
The email link in my YouTube is active, yes.
Although I'm terrible at responding.
It's being like I'm getting completely spammed on that email.
So, it's a pain to go through.
And it's not like random people spamming.
It's like companies.
Sending random keys for random ass games, you know.
Even though I keep clicking on the unsubscribe thing.
It's just really swamping the whole thing.
Discord invitation doesn't work.
It should work.
Are you sure you're doing it right then?
It really should work.
If you see the one on...
On the channel.
If you go to any video and you go into the description, that link should work.
No, no, if you want something official, just send it to my mail.
I'll probably get around to it at some point.
Sure, you can send me an email.
I'm not going to guarantee a response though.
If you had to play one game for the rest of your life, which one would it be?
That is such an easy question.
It would be World of Warcraft Classic.
Even now, I want to play it.
In this very moment.
I would love to play it right now.
But it's very addicting.
And right now, I'm sort of waiting until the anniversary edition of...
Northrend?
What's it called?
Wrath of the Lich King is coming out.
I'm probably going to jump in and play it for a couple of months like I usually do, you know?
Why not Minecraft?
Because World of Warcraft is better.
Best game ever made, man.
The original, not the retail that is right now.
In my opinion.
Yes, I've heard of Piropito.
He's the guy that also did a very famous Let's Play of Minecraft.
And he's Japanese.
Totally thought you were going to say Breath of the Wild.
Really?
Interesting.
Why?
Ever tried Old School RuneScape?
Yeah, but at that point it was called RuneScape.
And I only played a little bit.
This was back in my high school times.
I'm surprised Jackie isn't jumping up on the table today.
I just noticed she hasn't done that once today.
Maybe she's intimidated by all my anime voices.
Kingdom Come Deliverance, I definitely want to play.
I heard very good things about both games, especially the second one.
They're apparently excellent.
Extraction Shooters?
Yes, I've actually played one on my channel.
I've played...
Man, why am I blanking on these game names right now?
The recent one, Ark Raiders.
It's like 14 or so episodes.
I also briefly played Escape from Tarkov many, many years ago.
Got completely overwhelmed.
Wasn't really for me, didn't really enjoy that much.
It was very janky and didn't run well.
It felt like a mess.
Wasn't for me.
What else?
Maybe it's different nowadays.
Back then it was definitely an experience.
Guys, thank you so much for watching.
I'm going!
And then next time it's going to be Minecraft.
And then probably a new game for stream.
I should think about that one though.
I haven't decided yet.
But something!
I'll see you around.
Have a wonderful Sunday.
Bye-bye!
One bean for the road.
Bean.
Yeah!
See you around.